Greetings earthlings!
How's it going?
How's everybody doing?
I just look at chat wasn't last stream a dying stream?
Yes, it was.
I had massive troubles last stream and I got my ass kicked.
But I come with good news because I intend to not get my ass kicked today.
Today we shall persevere.
And even if we don't persevere, I'm still gonna mentally persevere.
That's the goddamn plan.
And it's gonna be glorious.
What's up, Abi Kadabra.
I love your name.
Great.
Cats on my lap and you're streaming?
Ah, thank you.
Would love to a cat on my lap.
I've always wanted a cat.
You're doing... oops!
How you doing, man?
You're doing great?
I'm also doing good, man.
I'm going to look at a new apartment the day after tomorrow.
I'm excited to see what that apartment is all about.
Maybe I'll get it.
Maybe not.
We'll have to see.
But I have to move, so.
I'm looking forward to that.
What's up, Palicado?
Neuterpog.
Haven't caught the last couple streams, so glad to be here for this one.
You know what?
You should be okay that you missed the last stream, okay?
That's all I'm gonna say.
I may or may not have done very well.
Let's just leave it at that.
I thought you were saying Hy-Vee.
Oh, you're talking to Hive.
No, you're talking to Kyali, who was talking to Hive.
Oh my god.
What's up, Lalvi?
And Raven Warrior, the vapid version.
Well, a new apartment in the sense that I'm going to move.
Not a new apartment, as in it's more new than the one I have now.
It's okay.
The evidence of your failings will be on YouTube soon.
It actually already is.
Yeah.
Feels bad, man.
Sometimes I wish I could... Oops!
Forgot to save that VOD, you know.
Don't know where that went.
You know what?
I did actually discover some interesting things in the last stream.
I discovered that you get a chest if you don't kill anything.
I did a little bit more translating.
And I also, by the way, discovered something that I want to try again regarding the re-roll.
Because I somehow bugged and saved some money with a re-roll.
I'm going to try and replicate it today if I find the means for it.
I have some ideas, but I'm going to do that.
For a second, I thought the smoke on the starting screen was real smoke being reflected in my monitor.
Oh no!
Imagine you're just sitting there and the apartment's on fire in the background.
Oh, that's horrible.
Sorry I laughed at that, but that was kind of funny.
Control the YouTube audience.
What did you translate so far?
I didn't translate anything really.
I just... Oh, so when I say translate, what I meant is that I have an alphabet, right?
I just added more letters to it.
Yeah, that's it.
The thing is, I died so much last time, I didn't really get to anywhere where I could translate.
I died before that could happen.
It was rapid fire dying last time.
How do we request 7 TV mode?
I don't know if that's a thing you can request.
You can let me know which one you would like to add on Discord or something and I can try and add it as long as it's appropriate.
What's today's drink?
It is actually a Coke Zero.
I opened it before I started.
Mr. Beat 93.
By the way, every time I read your name, I think of Mr. Beast.
Is that intentional or... I try my hardest not to say Mr. Beast every time I read your name, but it's just a Coke Zero.
Yeah, I got a little thirsty beforehand, so I did open it.
I did.
Yes.
But wait a minute, don't I have the fake can somewhere?
I can play a fake can for you.
If I still have it.
This is so dumb.
I think it's gone.
Yeah, too bad.
That's what I mean.
Yeah, just on the channel.
It was actually called channel related channel on Discord.
Something there.
Yeah.
Okay, guys, I am ready to die some more, because let's be honest, it's gonna happen.
I gotta get some warm up deaths in there.
That's to be expected.
So let me switch over.
Let's just double check everything's working.
Nice.
It's working.
Let me see if my thing is working.
Fantastic.
Now I switch back.
Okay, here we go.
It's new game time, because I am dead.
I'm very dead.
And I will try the daily run at some point.
Don't worry, I will try it.
Just not today.
I still have things I need to do in this world.
Okay.
I feel like I should start to become a little superstitious in this game.
You know?
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
You know what?
If you get hit that quick in the beginning, it's a good sign.
Superstition dictates that that means you get a good run.
It's like, if you have so much bad misfortune early on, you can only have good ones later, you know?
It's only logical.
And you can't tell me that's not logical.
Whoa.
Okay, good.
So I'm gonna go grab the tablet.
That is a must.
And if I cannot kill Stuart, then I won't.
I'll just save it.
He does not need to die immediately.
Even though I really want to kill him immediately, he does not need to die immediately.
I need to stay disciplined here.
That is the way forward.
Also, I'm carrying water and chaotic polymorphy.
Water.
Let me... Wait, what is going on here?
Why is there all these barrels of water?
There's so much water.
Is this like a water modifier that we have on right now?
Wait, how do I get to the tablet?
It must be down here somewhere, I guess.
I'm gonna blow a hole through there.
Yeah, that's good.
Nice.
Ooh, it's water.
Uh, actually, I can get through with this.
Yeah.
Aww.
Okay, but that's gonna burn, so...
Oh my god.
The game just does not want me to go this way.
That's clear.
Blow it.
Here we go.
Hmm.
Oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
So we make a hole and then the water is gonna... Oh, there's no water in there.
Oh, there is.
Okay, nice.
Turn it all to water.
Beautiful.
Ah!
Careful.
Hmm.
Explosion.
Water.
And candles.
Beastwax.
I learned the other day that beastwax is another word for business in some circles.
My English repertoire is slowly increasing.
What does that sound I just heard?
That's a sound I haven't heard before.
Sounded like a dinosaur.
Get that extra money.
Doing.
Hey, guys.
Oh, that was close.
You can actually tell when they're about to jump, they make a little sound before they jump.
I never noticed that.
They go like puk or something.
Too risky.
Good amount of money, though.
Now I will kill with tablet, whatever I can.
Like, like now.
Oi, that's bad.
That's actually kind of... Did I somehow hit him still?
That's incredible.
Don't hit me.
Nice.
I'm getting good with that.
I really am.
Whoa, I blocked his shot with it, too.
I guess I can use it as a makeshift shield.
If I really need to.
Not bad.
Sweet.
What if they kill themselves?
I wonder if that counts as an accident.
I mean, they definitely did not intend to kill themselves, so it should be an accident, right?
Oh, he's coming here.
The more I practice with the tablet, the better I will become against Stuart as well.
You know, like, I just need to get the physics of it down intuitively.
And at that point, I shall become unstoppable.
Can I break with that?
I cannot.
Oh, sick.
Great start.
I do wonder... So, I know there's a seed associated with every, what do you call it?
New game you make.
I wonder if the stuff contained in a chest is determined when you destroy it or open it, or if it's determined already, like, when you start the game.
You know what I mean?
So, like, because there's a daily run, everyone gets the same.
I wonder if people have different chests and stuff.
I want to get in here.
Actually, I don't want to get in there.
I just want to make it into water.
Got oil here.
Not anything I would like.
Whoa!
You guys came out of nowhere.
By the way, I'm starting to think maybe I should drink more alcohol when I play this game.
Because last time I did, I drank two IPAs and I immediately had the best run of my life.
So, I don't know, man.
That feels like maybe I should do that, you know?
The statistics are there.
To support it.
Well, it's very low number statistics, but still.
Toxic Rock and Pete.
We hang out at the Corova Milk Bar.
That is Pete.
I forgot the other names.
I usually remember that.
My brain is not working right now.
Sir?
Do you want that?
You do not want that.
Can you stop?
There we go.
Look how safe I'm playing.
I'll take that.
Thanks.
Make some fire there.
Seems good to me.
What do we have up here?
Not much of interest.
Could go downstairs while I wait for that to burn.
Oh, hello.
That could blow up that as well.
Let's be ultra careful.
Ultra careful.
Oh, nice.
You know what?
I have 10 of these left.
I should just dig if they go like that.
Hey, walk into it.
Come here.
He's too smart.
Oh, it doesn't even dig?
Wow.
And now for the tablet.
Oh, that didn't work out.
That's okay.
See, that also dropped two gold.
So whenever something explodes, it counts.
I should water myself a little bit and grab that.
Nice.
I do actually think that there is a real effect when it comes to alcohol.
Where if I'm sober, like a million things go through my brain at all times.
And it's a lot of trouble to keep track of one specific thing at times.
Like I get distracted so easily.
Whereas when I have a bit of alcohol in my system, I feel like I am more able to focus on one thing at a time.
It sounds a bit unintuitive, but I think that's true.
I've had a lot of that experience in my life.
It's like information overload and I, my brain can't handle it when I try to focus on everything at once.
Let me go around.
Yeah, that's the access point I was looking for.
And we... Oh, hello.
Oh, wow.
That still killed them.
You don't need a lot of momentum for those guys.
Oh, I... Ooh, a chest.
Why did that immediately start doing that?
What the fuck is that?
Huh?
Summon portal?
Wait.
Summon a strange portal?
What the fuck does that mean?
Okay, I'm already mega excited.
What the hell?
Boink.
Okay, but I can't use it yet.
I need to find a wand.
But that is very intriguing.
Man, can I even... Oh, wait.
I have an explosive right here.
I'm so dumb.
Oh, I should take care of that guy first.
Don't get hit.
Okay, nice.
There.
Blow it.
Amazing.
What's that?
Oh, it's gold.
Man, I have a lot of gold.
It's going really well.
Hello.
Let me see how much I can do with this tablet against this dude.
Okay.
That was kind of a slow throw, I guess.
Didn't do much.
Nice.
Water myself.
Grab that.
Very nice.
Oh, careful, careful.
There's a wand.
Okay, that's not a bad wand.
0.05 castalay?
I'll take it.
That is decent.
Whoops.
Oh, I see you.
Maybe it's time for some good old water.
Water flows downhill, right?
So, have fun.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
What?
I do wonder if that counts as an accident.
I mean, I supplied the water, but he stepped in it.
This is starting to sound like some kind of trial.
Doink.
Oh, nice.
Fantastic.
This guy has mega much HP somehow.
I'm stuck.
Careful, careful.
Wait, what?
There's poison in my bottle?
No, wait, that wasn't.
I'm so confused.
I'm very low HP here.
I'm gonna grab this wand and get the hell out.
An energy sphere with a shuffle.
Do I like that more than this?
I think I do, because this one has a terrible recharge.
Yeah.
All right, let's leave.
I'm playing it safe.
Okay, let's heal.
And see what we got.
We got a lot of money.
Nice.
That's a good start.
Is that...
Is that... I can't... Hold on, is that the same as this?
It is.
Okay, so it's not the energy.
This is energy sphere.
It's not energy orb.
Right.
No more shuffle.
Most of the wands will be non-shuffling.
The wands you carry with you turn into non-shufflers too.
Most of the wands will be... I feel like this is not a bad perk.
I never tried it.
Oh, but I also... Oh, dude, before I do that, I actually want to try something.
This is what I was talking about.
Okay, so hold on.
I need to buy this one.
Let me also put this here.
Oh, but fuck.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're gonna make someone mad if we do that.
Hold up.
Nope, we're not doing that.
We're not doing that.
I was gonna black hole and let this thing fall down again, because last time it stayed at 200.
When we went to the next holy mountain, I rerolled there.
I came back here.
This was still 200.
I need to try and replicate that at some point, but I'm not gonna do it now because I'm afraid of Stuart and I don't have the means of killing him.
Or do I?
Let me see if I can make something.
That one is definitely something we need to buy.
Like without question.
Put these here.
I only need one or two.
Let me put one up here and one there.
Also, I gotta try this.
Ah, please don't kill me.
Oh, wait.
Did I try this once before?
No, that was with the... that was an eldritch portal, wasn't it?
I'm gonna put it on a distance to be safe here.
Oh, it's shuffled.
Hold up.
Seven uses.
Uh, let's try it.
Let's try it.
Really?
It actually was a portal.
Oh, I should have jumped in.
I have six left.
Okay, so I don't want to jump in this yet in case I can't come back.
So what I'm gonna do first here is to do everything I need to do in this holy mountain and then I'm gonna try and jump through the portal.
That's the plan.
Give me this one.
And put this up there.
That's nice actually.
Luminous drill.
Very solid.
0.13.
It's not the best wand ever there.
Let me see these wands.
Shuffle.
I wonder if I take that perk over there if all of these will also turn into or some of them will turn into non-shuffle that were shuffled before.
That's actually a decent wand in itself.
I just heard a train whistle.
Am I... hold on.
The fuck?
There's no trains where I live.
I'm so confused.
Whatever.
Okay, so this one we wait with that.
I'm tempted to just... Oh, what is Angry Ghost again?
An angry spirit comes to your aid, copying nearby spell.
I... no, see that seems dangerous.
I'm gonna try this.
We're gonna try new perks, right?
We're trying them all.
Let's see if these changed.
Oh!
Hey!
They... they did!
Look!
All of them are non-shuffle!
That's insanity!
Yo!
That's crazy!
So wait, it did say most, didn't it?
Yeah, most of the wands will be non-shuffling.
Oh, that's awesome!
So wait, from here on out?
Oh, we're gonna be finding crazy wands then.
Maybe this is a pretty good perk.
0.13.
So wait, what do I have now?
That's a good wand.
Was this shuffle before?
I don't remember.
Anyway, so I need to... so a digging wand?
Luminous drill.
That seems maybe good.
But we need something with a very low... that one.
I need that one.
Oh, but it runs out so quick.
Shit.
Okay.
Even slower.
Also not that great.
No, no, no, no.
Switch this back.
Put it here.
Okay, that's not bad.
That's okay.
And then... what does this do?
Add some cast delay, reduce your spread.
Okay.
I'm gonna pick up one more of these.
Uh, I should buy this one too, I think.
Just because.
It has some of this stuff.
Burning trail.
So now that I have a trigger and a double spell...
No, I actually have a triple.
Dude, I can actually make something.
I can make something decent here.
I have the means.
So wait, let me see the best one for this.
With a decently load.
That one.
Oh, but the mana charge is terrible.
All right, fine.
I'm gonna be using this one.
Into a triple.
And what do we want to payload into this?
It's like a delivery mechanism.
We're gonna be using...
That's not bad.
Three of them.
I could not add burning trail.
Shit.
What if... Oh, hold up, hold up, hold up.
We can make it better.
So this is kind of fast.
But if I do this, it's even faster.
It doesn't matter where it goes.
Yeah, I like that.
I like that.
Dude,
what about this?
That seems pretty cool.
Think about it.
It's the same mana drain, but it does more damage.
It does add a little bit of cast to it, but so do these.
Oh, but this also adds crit chance.
Oh, hold up now.
Okay, that's kind of slow.
I think I like this.
Or maybe we do one of each.
Just a crazy ass delivery here, you know?
Express delivery package.
Yeah, that seems fine.
Not bad.
What about the energy sphere?
No, that's not worth it.
Not worth it.
We have X and something that doesn't matter.
All right, I think we are good to go.
Then we have a one that can dig.
That could be that one, I guess.
Why not?
Or that one.
No, this one is good.
That goes there.
And then I want to try this now.
I'm just gonna cast it where I stand and try and jump in immediately.
See what happens.
Why not?
Right?
Yeah.
And then also perks I took.
Good.
All right, let's try it.
Let me fill out my water bottle.
And then it's time.
Let's go.
Take me.
Oh, wait.
Ooh, okay, hold on.
I think I know what to do.
If you notice, it's building up.
We need to extend the duration of this somehow.
We need to... like, this one goes out before it manages to make the portal itself.
So we have to extend the duration somehow.
And there's spells for that or modifiers, so I just gotta find them.
Okay, but this is pretty cool.
I like it, I like it.
Let's go.
Oh my goodness.
Right there.
Thank you.
That's so nice.
I feel so blessed.
Oopsie.
It's you.
Am I even doing any proper damage here?
It doesn't look like I'm doing that much damage.
Maybe my setup isn't that great.
Damn, that was a lot of gold.
Holy crap.
Holy cannoli.
Wait, why is that here now?
Wasn't it here?
Oh, that's weird.
I probably just don't remember.
Oh, that's weird the way it digs randomly.
I kind of like it.
Aha.
That's a use for the black hole.
And in fact, I'm going to do it like this.
Just so I don't break the brickwork and make people angry.
Nice.
Sweet.
Saw blade.
On bombs?
Yeah, I don't know about that one, bro.
I mean, I'll take it, but I don't know about that one.
That's all I'm saying.
Saw blades are scary.
Wait, it feels like I'm not doing damage sometimes when I shoot this.
That's another black hole.
A triple spell and a freeze charge.
I like the triple spell.
Maybe I like it more than this.
Also, I have to remember, most of these are non shuffle now.
Oh man, the wand is not bad itself.
This is actually a decent wand.
96 mana charge, 380 mana max.
That is really good.
I think I have great opportunities to find a good wand.
Oh wow, see that instantly killed them.
But then sometimes they do no damage at all.
It's a bit weird.
Play it safe.
Oh man, you know those days when you just feel clean?
That's how I feel today.
It's hard to explain, but it's like you're sitting here and you just feel clean.
It's so dumb you say it out loud.
I mean, it did take a shower, but it's not like that.
I mean, it is, but it's also something more.
It's like your body is healthy feeling.
No, you had a good meal.
It wasn't greasy.
It was nice.
And you feel light on your feet.
It's just nice.
How did I get hit?
God damn it.
Sometimes I tried so hard to dodge that I actually get hit because I tried too hard.
Whereas I should have just stood still.
Oh, what a combination.
Can I not?
I don't want to use a black hole for this, but what I do want to do is this watch.
Oh, that would have been so sick.
Asshole.
Come here.
My opportunity is gone.
This would have worked beautifully if it worked.
It didn't work.
Unless I can get it back up.
There's no way in the air.
No, it's not going to work.
That would have been funny though.
That was my one opportunity.
I could burn... No, that's not going to help me.
I could dig with this, but it's going to be a random dig.
Sometimes it's... No, it's not going to work.
Nevermind.
Terrible idea.
Like, I do have a luminous drill in my wand, so technically it could work.
Ain't nobody got time for that though.
I think the luminous drill is not actually hitting them sometimes.
Let me think.
I should... Oh, he has a wand.
Hold up.
This is scary.
Oh, dude, I can freeze him.
Wait, did he just summon that?
Oh, he had an egg.
That makes sense.
That makes a lot of sense.
I don't want an egg.
Weird how they're my friends now.
Shouldn't they be his friends?
Uh, sir.
Are you allowed to throw those chemicals?
Have you gotten the proper permissions?
I don't think so.
In fact, pheromone could be nice to have.
But I have unstable teleportation.
I kinda need to get rid of it first.
I also have chaotic... I have the worst potions!
I'm carrying dangerous stuff here.
I'm gonna empty it in here.
I'm more afraid of polymorphine than I am of, uh, teleportation.
Although I did get teleported into a sea of lava once.
On accident.
Or by accident.
Fuck!
My mind can't make up what sounds more correct.
On accident or by accident, you know?
Give me pheromone.
I need it for friendo in Heezy Base.
I guess they're my friends now.
And it will last forever.
There's a chest!
I'm gonna black hole it.
Ooh, it almost sucked up the chest.
Oh, that's a Kiva Skivi.
Not interested in that, unfortunately.
What is that, though?
Is that mana?
I think it is.
I don't want it.
There's wax again.
I feel like I'm starting to see more wax.
More than usual.
Next.
Oh, he's a friend.
Not bad.
Where to now?
Let me check the water.
I can't even get in.
Should I just go?
No, I have 120 HP.
I can't go back and change my wands.
That's something to keep in mind.
So whatever I pick up in here needs to come with me.
I'm gonna explore a bit more.
Especially because we still have fungal caverns.
And there could be some nice wands there.
In fact, it's kind of a high-risk, high-reward place.
And it's only worth doing when you have a lot of HP.
Oh, here we go.
What's this?
Magic arrow with timer, spirit bolt, slithering path.
You know what?
I'm kind of curious to see how that will work with a black hole.
That seems very interesting.
Dang it.
I could try unstable teleportation.
To get on the other side of that wall.
But that's a bit risky.
Is that mine?
I think that's my old wand.
Whoa.
Good.
All right, so I only explored the right side.
Not get too close.
That's okay.
I never took the spell refresh, so I could go get more black holes if I need to.
Okay, a wand.
Come on, be something great.
I need the best.
Ooh, actually.
That's a sick wand.
Look at the stats on that.
I'm taking it.
That's an even better wand.
Wait, I already went that way.
Oh no.
How am I gonna...
How on earth am I gonna get through here?
I should get the spell refresh.
I don't see any other way.
I feel like I'm locked in.
Yeah.
What a chance I'm coming back here anyway.
I'm probably gonna die, right?
So may as well...
Made it.
Nice.
And here I should be able to get through.
Albeit with a bit of resistance.
It's gonna be very annoying.
Yeah, fall down, fall down, fall down.
There we go.
Need to angle it in a weird way, such that the luminous drill actually hits the right things here.
See, that's good.
Did I make it?
Yeah, nice.
And I shouldn't buy anything else, I don't think.
Gimme.
I'm really curious about that portal.
I need to find a way to use that.
Oh wait, that also refreshes the portal.
Oh, so I actually have a lot of tries with that, I guess.
I also kind of want to try just spamming it.
Maybe you need multiples at the same time to charge up the portal or something.
I'm gonna go through here, I think.
Go.
Have a nice bath.
Was that an ear?
And another dead end.
But if we are smart here, we can burn it.
Yeah, that's nice.
And while that's happening, I'm gonna go over here and see if I can't get to that wand.
But it's embedded in the rock.
There's no way unless I use a portal.
Firebolt with trigger.
I don't think so.
Nah.
Not feeling that.
And now we gain access to up here as well, that's lovely.
Wow, that died quick.
Oh, the fungal caverns are leaking.
96 to Stanley Bay.
Here we go.
Let's see if we can't find some wands in here.
Or some hearts, either would make me happy.
The problem is I can't dig at all, so that's very bad.
Also, they're being pushed around a lot because of the puff of air I have.
Actually really effective against melee people.
But also a little chaotic.
Because you can't keep them where you want them to be.
Those guys are going to be annoying, as always.
There's a wand up there.
I have one black hole left.
I see a mage.
What kind of a mage is that?
Kind of just want to observe him and see what he does.
Are you down here?
Uh-oh.
That's actually good for me right now.
Not bad.
Uh-oh.
There's enemies everywhere.
This is just so scary.
Did he just make a way through here?
My dude!
Thank you!
What do we got?
Energy orbs.
That's big.
But the wand is shitty.
Oh man, I can't replace this wand.
This wand is too good.
At least for now.
Let's see what else we got in here.
I could get high.
That's a risk.
No.
There's actually wands everywhere.
In fact, in every fungal place, there seems to be a lot of wands.
Ambrosia.
Let's get rid of... come on.
Gently put it down now.
Gently put it down here.
It's so scary.
Okay, I can't get in there.
Hmm.
I do have one black hole.
Where to use it?
Maybe here.
This one seems more hard to get to, so that seems maybe more... worth it.
We'll have to see.
Uh-oh, there's a frog.
Also, he's going berserk now.
So am I.
Okay.
Nice spells, but no thanks.
I'm gonna try find one more wand, and then I'm out of here.
That's a dead end.
Oh, he has a wand!
Nice!
Access achieved.
That is... is that teleportation?
Why won't my cursor tell me?
I'm mousing over it, damn it!
That's so annoying!
It is.
It is teleportation.
Okay.
Let's not touch that.
Yo!
Oh!
Okay, yeah, this one needs to be taken.
I am gonna...
Hold on.
Throw away my black hole.
It's that much worth it.
Yeah.
And then I'm gonna get high.
Because why not?
Oh, fuck, that's an enemy.
Got him.
Are we tripping enough?
Oh, we are.
Diamond.
So that means...
Diamond has become something else.
Ooh, what could that be?
I wonder...
Sir?
Oh, he's the teleporter, man.
Okay, I will just quickly see what's down here.
Unstable.
That's bad.
That potion is scary.
There's two wands right here.
I gotta check them out.
I gotta.
No.
And there's a wand there.
I could swim in there.
Are there any enemies to bother me?
Luminous drills.
No.
Nope.
I think we're good.
This guy needs to die.
And he bleeds this crap too.
That is very displeasing.
What's that down there?
Wait a second.
Did Diamond get turned into a...
Oh no, it would tell me.
It usually says transformed, actually.
Yeah, never mind.
It would say transformed.
I guess I gotta keep an eye on that.
All right.
Let's move.
I'm not gonna heal yet.
Wait a second.
Although that is the big teleport.
Nice.
Very nice.
And what do we have here?
More love.
Boomerang spells.
That's the one that gives them extra damage.
Extra wand capacity.
Creatures become more friendly towards each other.
I don't remember if I ever tried this one.
I think I tried it once, but I wasn't quite sure what was up with that, but I'm gonna try it again.
We're trying new perks.
At least I think new perks.
Oh, then we have these amazing spells now.
Put them up here.
And a formation pentagon.
Wow.
All kinds of crap.
Unstable crystals.
Leave them here for now.
And the portal goes up here for now.
Okay, so we can do something crazy.
Watch this.
This is the wand.
This is the biggie.
It's kind of small too in a way.
There's not that many slots, but you know what I mean.
It's biggie smalls.
Damage plus.
No.
Trigger into damage plus.
Into speed.
We may not have enough mana for this.
That's the one caveat here.
Let's go.
Oh, we don't even have room for that.
I guess triple.
Uh, we can keep it simple.
Just to see.
Keep it low mana.
Let's see how much damage this does.
Put it, yeah.
That's that's a solid amount of damage right there.
And you know what?
I may not even need the speed.
You know, the speed is nice, but it's not like necessarily needed here.
And what if I put this inside of...
Let me see the difference.
42.
It's the same.
Oh, no, no, no, wait, wait.
Six.
Yeah, sometimes they...
No, is it because I'm...
Wait, I don't understand.
Yeah, I don't think it changes anything.
But I'm gonna try this instead.
So this cast costs five mana.
This costs one mana.
That's actually a big deal.
But it's not a big deal because...
Oh, this actually reduces spread.
And I can even throw in more.
We could put in...
I don't even know.
Did the drill.
I guess.
How about that?
Wait, what?
That looks crazy to me.
Like, this won't make me go oom.
It won't.
But I don't like...
I don't like the drill there, honestly.
I don't like the fact that it randomly drills.
That makes me unhappy.
I'm gonna find another...
Oh, we also have this, of course.
Forgot about that.
Let's try it.
Oh, of course!
This is what we're doing!
It costs one mana!
God damn!
Forgot about that one.
Holy crap.
One, two...
Three, four...
Oh, shit.
It's not gonna show me the damage now.
It's a little too slow now.
So we could do this just to make it a little faster.
Actually, that doesn't do shit.
Why doesn't that help?
What are we limited by?
Castelae?
Really?
So wait, wait, wait, hold on.
This has 0.18...
Hold up, something's wrong.
This adds 0.05.
Oh, this also adds 0.08.
Hold up now.
Let me try and understand.
This...
Okay, so recharge time is definitely zero, because look, all these three reduce by 0.17.
So we are limited by cast, but this one reduces by 0.58!
How?
Wait, why is this not a machine gun?
What?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Let me just...
Dump, dump, dump, dump.
Okay, now if I do this...
Huh?
Why doesn't that work?
I'm losing my mind.
Wait, is it because...
No, it's nothing to do with my perks.
What?
Hold up a second.
Castelae 0.18.
Recharge time 0.18.
Recharge time is being reduced by 0.17, so it's practically zero.
And even more so.
It's zero now, and it's zero on castelae.
What if I remove this?
Okay.
Wait.
Okay, so that makes sense.
That also makes sense, because now I'm essentially only doing castelae here.
If I add two of these...
All right.
But if I add this, then it's super...
What if I change it?
So hold on, it's 0.18.
0.05 gets added.
So we are at 0.23.
Oh, actually that makes sense.
Then we reduce recharge time, so that's zero, but we still have 0.23 castelae.
So now we need to remove that, and we can do that with...
That one.
So this is the order.
Nope.
I don't get it.
I don't fucking get it.
I don't understand.
What am I...
Huh?
Why doesn't that work?
So that makes sense.
It's zero on both counts now.
This is an insane lightsaber, basically.
There's gotta be...
There's gotta...
I don't...
I don't get it.
I really don't.
I am so confused.
What if I do this?
Change it.
Nothing.
Now add this.
Now do this.
Put it outside.
I feel like I am losing my mind.
I don't understand this game.
I don't understand what's going on.
Why is this not working?
It does say it has some magical properties.
And that's what I don't understand.
Well.
Also has some magical properties.
Maybe the damage it does is also magical in some way.
Maybe that's what that means.
Also has some magical properties.
This fucking chainsaw is breaking my brain, man.
It's been breaking my brain ever since I started this game.
So, hold on.
This works.
Why doesn't this simple setup work?
Let's think about this.
So these are the stats.
It's being modified with this.
Right?
Stats are zero now.
Okay.
Stats are zero.
Then this comes in.
It adds a little bit of castelay.
But, even if it adds 0.05.
That's not 0.05.
That's way more than 0.05.
That feels really slow.
There's something wrong here.
Okay, let me try.
I mean, fuck it.
Let's just run.
I mean, whatever.
Whatever.
What I really need is the quick...
Quick, whatever the fuck it's called, spell.
The one that reduces...
Because that one works.
You know?
Maybe it's something to do with the fact that this is a projectile.
And the quick recharge is a modifier.
Maybe that's what's happening here.
I think I'm misunderstanding exactly.
So when it says castelay minus 0.58.
And recharge time minus 0.17.
Apparently that does not affect the wand.
Even though I thought it did.
So it's doing something else because it's a projectile.
Maybe it's only doing that for the next projectile.
And then when the next projectile gets shot.
This is still back.
Oh, actually, maybe that makes sense.
So, okay.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I think I understand.
So, look, instant, right?
Okay, so the castelay is 0.18.
Recharge time is the same.
With this, it's pretty much zero, right?
And if I only have this here, when I shoot this luminous drill, it shoots once.
Like, right?
And then the next time it shoots, it starts over.
But the stats are still being reduced because it's only this.
Maybe it only reduces for the next one in line.
Yeah, that has to be what happens.
That has to be what happens.
But why doesn't this work?
So, this is also a spell.
What if I try this one?
It's the same.
Interesting.
And if I do this...
Oh, you know what?
I need another luminous drill then, I guess.
That is the way to do it.
What?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on, I have a better idea.
We're gonna be triggering at the end here.
One, two...
No, wait, it doesn't work like that.
Hold on.
I need to do this.
Oh, this is it!
I bet you that works now.
Never mind.
Okay, hold on.
Actually, put it back.
Let me check these away for a second.
The crazy thing is, I feel like I solved this ages ago.
And now suddenly it doesn't work anymore.
Did the game get updated or something?
I don't understand.
I feel like the game has changed.
Let me try this.
I actually had a triple, I didn't realize.
Do it now.
It's still slow, but if I add this at the end...
What am I limited by?
So I'm limited by cast delay right now.
And this one reduces recharge time.
Fuck, I need something that reduces cast delay.
This increases...
Actually, this increases projectile speed.
Hey!
Hey, that's not bad!
Hold up a second.
What does this look like?
Okay, so it is kind of a big amplitude on that wave, I guess.
I was expecting a smaller amplitude.
But the fact that it increases the speed is actually a decently cool thing here.
And when you shoot like...
Let's say you have a machine gun and you go brrrr!
You're essentially gonna be doing a lot of AOE effects with that.
Maybe that is a good-ass spell!
It even costs zero mana!
I like that it has to signify at the end like a snake.
Lovely description there.
Okay.
Well, so last...
What did I do last time to make this work?
I had this, right?
No, actually I had a triple, I'm pretty sure.
Or a double.
And then I just did this.
And that worked.
It worked.
But I guess the di- Oh, this is actually a little bit faster.
Put this in here.
Hmm.
Oh, maybe put one outside.
I don't fucking understand.
Give me another, uh, trigger.
Is that faster?
I'm losing my damn mind.
Dude, I swear to you!
Last time I had a trigger with a double and chainsaws, and that's it.
No, that's not true.
I had a quick recharge as well, but...
Yeah, okay, that's what I had, I guess.
I had a quick recharge.
So I guess I can't do that now.
Fuck!
But that's fine.
I mean, I'm still doing a lot of damage.
It's not bad, you know?
Like, by all means, this is great.
That costs one mana?
How much does the triple cost?
Two mana!
Okay, so it's actually better to have this.
Like, that is a good amount of damage.
You know?
That's a good amount of damage.
I could even add some...
stuff like this.
And I guess it doesn't matter where these are in here.
Wait, is that actually making a- Oh no, I need to put this out here.
There!
That's what I need to do.
Speed on the spark bolt.
Oh yeah.
If I want to do it like that, that's how you should do it.
Uh, okay.
Let me see what else I have.
Burst of air.
I don't want these things.
Let me put the burst of air here.
I don't think I want to use that.
That makes me unhappy.
Um, I feel like I should maybe put this in here because the mana is already quite managed.
So if I put this here, it's a little better.
Yeah, that seems good.
And that is more damage, I think.
I broke the statue.
Great.
Poison arc.
Don't think I want to- Ooh!
No, this is 80 mana.
There's no way.
No way.
These can go here.
Although, hold on.
They do add crit, right?
I wonder if that crit is being added to the chainsaw as well, or if it's only the spell.
I'll have to think about that.
I need some kind of simple test to make.
What if I have a double?
I have no clue.
But this is fine because I'm still actually not consuming all of my mana.
I could be doing a little more damage.
Dum dum dum.
It's the same amount as- Like, this doesn't- Wait, let me think.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is being affected every- Okay, I need to look at the board.
So when I- Okay, let's make this super simple.
When I shoot, this is what's being shot, right?
And it's being shot with these stats.
Except we are reducing recharge time.
So that means it's the cast delay that's the bottling, right?
Okay, good.
And we even add some cast delay here.
So the cast delay is 0.26.
Uh, no, it's 0.31 actually.
This is 0.31 cast delay, I believe.
Okay.
It's 0.31 cast delay, so can we reduce that?
So if I put this here, why won't that reduce the cast delay for this spell being cast, which is, in essence, all of this?
Why doesn't that work?
I fucking give up.
I don't want to think about this anymore.
This is also one less mana.
I'm using that.
Although I could go for that.
I have the mana for it, right?
Wait, why is that suddenly so...
Wait a minute, that's better.
Hold up.
One, two, three.
That's faster!
Is it not?
I'm breaking my brain here.
I don't know.
Didn't I have a chainsaw in the beginning at some point?
I feel like I had that.
What?
No.
Huh?
Oh.
Didn't I have something like this?
I remember having a chainsaw in the beginning.
Aw, it's pissing me off, dude!
I feel like I did this once before!
I can't move on.
I gotta get to the bottom of this.
I'm losing my mind.
This is so annoying.
I'm... I'm... It's on the tip of my tongue here.
It's on the tip of my damn tongue.
Is it the wand?
Is it bugged?
Because I put the shuffle to non-shuffle, but somehow it's...
Broke it, maybe?
No.
No way.
This, this, this...
Nah, I give up.
Fuck it.
We move on.
I don't give a shit.
Put it on this one and put an extra chainsaw.
There it is.
That's the damage we do.
That's it.
Let's go.
I don't give a fuck anymore.
I've lost my damn mind.
Okay, I'm doing good damage.
That's the good news here.
I have no idea what I did last time.
Maybe I... Maybe I don't have the means to do what I did once before.
I just feel like I had the same things last time that I do now.
But I couldn't tell you.
My brain broke from that.
I lost 20 IQ through all of that.
Ugh, that's annoying, man.
I'm gonna go left first.
And if I find some hearts, I'm gonna go back and heal.
That's the plan.
Okay, that's good.
That's not bad damage by any means there.
That's really nice.
I mean, yeah.
I have some extras.
Or I mean empty wands, so I can afford to pick up some stuff.
Also, I forgot to put this in my bar before I moved on.
I was so frustrated, I just wanted to move on.
Forgot about it.
Oh, no, no, you don't.
No, you don't.
Where'd you come from?
I cleared the right side, you bastard.
Also, look at all the blood I'm producing now, because I have chainsaws.
It's kind of a striking difference.
The chainsaws do indeed make people bleed.
Oh,
no, there's wands everywhere and I can't get to it.
I feel like this is actually a super weird run.
I haven't been able to find any proper digging here.
Or at least make something nice.
Digging has been problematic.
Where are these fucking things coming from?
Are they appearing out of the snow here or what?
Oh, here we go.
Now we can find some HP in here.
Oh, yeah, good damage.
I really need some light.
I'm just gonna ignore most enemies and go left.
I think I'm hitting something.
He's bleeding sand.
This is nerve-racking.
Did I hit him?
I got that guy.
Whoa.
Oh, you absolute bastard.
I got him.
I heard him go.
I'm very low HP.
This is kind of risky.
It's very risky.
Got a dude up there.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no.
Shit.
5 HP.
Oh, my goodness.
Just grab the heart.
There's also a wand.
There we go.
That's a digging wand, but I don't like that there's a timer on it.
That is so expensive.
50.
But it's better than whatever I have here.
Wait, what?
What?
Oh, no.
Thank God there's no more range on that, huh?
Lord for that.
I'm leaving.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're going back to heal immediately.
We got the heart.
Yeah, let me go through here.
Making it as safe as possible.
Also, you know what?
I do have this.
Played ultra safe.
I forgot I had that, man.
Uh-oh.
So wait, these guys bleed diamonds, right?
Let's see what came out.
Oh, no.
I can't see what it is because there's gold in here.
Oh, it's teleportation.
Diamonds are teleportation.
Fuck.
Well, I guess it could have been worse.
Could have been worse.
But it's still pretty bad.
Wait, what's that wand?
Did I check that?
I did check that.
Let's just be safe here.
Wait, how do I get 21 HP?
I was at 5 HP before.
How did I heal?
I healed somehow.
What?
Did I?
I must have looked wrong.
Wow.
Dude, I am blind today.
I feel like my brain is not working.
I'm seeing shit.
I can't remember how to make wands.
It's a fucking disaster.
Oh, don't fall in that.
Yeah.
Oh, I made it.
Nice.
But look at this.
Why is that digging so much?
I mean, not digging.
Why is it bouncing so much?
That's not normally what happens.
Is it?
That thing doesn't...
Oh, wait, I understand why.
It's because they're Alzheimer's and they're put in parallel.
No, they're put in series.
That makes sense, actually.
At least I understand that.
All right, heal me up.
195, baby.
Oh, I forgot about this one as well.
Grabbing that immediately.
Shit, I can't...
Sparkly bounce?
Nah, that's bad.
Also, I am...
No, I can't...
Ah, fuck.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Let's go.
Oh.
That's a very interesting wand.
I don't want to use it like that.
Oh, there's an Ukuski in there.
Ukuski, Evie.
Speaking of Finnish.
The country, Finland.
Oh no, fuck, I'm an idiot.
I was about to say, a Finland person just won the biggest Starcraft tournament ever.
But that's not true.
I am wrong.
I'm just so used to that guy winning so much that I...
No, it wasn't him.
It was the other guy.
I don't want to spoil it if you haven't seen it yet.
Where are these rats coming from?
They're coming from areas that I've already cleared.
What's with the wind?
There's a very heavy wind right here.
Nice.
All things considered, it's not going too bad.
Like, this is workable.
Definitely.
Get to safety.
I see you down there.
Where's the emitter?
Somewhere down there.
Oi!
It was hard to dodge.
I should have let myself fall instead of jumping up.
Muscle memory dictates though, if you want to dodge, press the spacebar.
Not let go of the spacebar.
Why is that not broken yet?
There we go.
Sweet!
That is the skill I need to acquire.
Throwing boxes and shooting them in the air.
And I have 1,500 in the bank.
Very good.
Uh-oh.
I can't get in there.
I don't have the means.
That's the uku, skeevy.
No, it's actually a box, but still.
Don't want to go in there.
Also, I'm not noticing this more love perk.
I don't...
Okay, I guess enemies maybe fight less with each other?
That's something that is very hard to notice a difference in, I feel like.
I don't feel it.
I was practicing my downward dodge there.
Who's over there?
Oh, he died.
Okay, so now I'm here.
If only I had some digging, I could get a guaranteed heart.
Very good.
How am I doing so much damage?
It feels like I shouldn't be doing as much damage as I'm doing.
Like, I see the numbers on the screen and they're not that high.
But these guys, for example, I feel like they usually take way more damage before they die.
I'm probably just imagining things today.
Like, today has been weird, I guess.
My brain got off like 10 stations ago.
And it's going for a joyride right now.
I'm not in control.
Look at that, one shot at that guy.
Oh, he teleported away because he got hit by the blood of it.
Because diamond is now teleportation.
Very weird combination of things here.
Hold on, I'm going to try something here.
Oh, fuck.
Alright, okay, but I think I got some information there.
Let me see now.
What now?
Okay, so arrow's pointing down to the right.
Oh, fuck, wait.
Nope, hold on.
Oh, okay, so I'm back here now.
Wait a minute, where did the teleportation go?
Hello?
Oh, I'm in the wrong spot, I think.
Oh, I got teleported far.
Oh no, I teleported twice, I guess.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, interesting.
So, let me try something else.
If I jump from the left, from the right, I'm here.
And still pointing down to the right.
Teleportitis.
Hmm.
Wait a minute, where am I?
Hold on a minute, hold on a second.
Oh, I won.
Critical on wet enemies.
I feel like that could be so strong.
With the right, uh, spells.
Maybe I want that instead of this.
Yeah, give it.
Give me that.
Man, where's the teleportation?
Is it over here?
I have no idea.
Oh, careful there.
No idea, bro.
Rats are fucking falling from the sky here.
I'm not done.
Oh, don't want to hit that.
Okay, so if I now jump from the top...
What then?
Oh.
Wait, where am I?
I'm so...
Every time I get teleported, I am so confused.
Okay, so I'm...
I went to the right, okay.
Do you want something?
Wait a minute.
Are the rats friendly?
No.
Wait.
Ha!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This needs to be confirmed.
Is it the way I'm aiming?
I think it is!
Look!
Okay, so watch this.
I want to try and get in here.
Oh, wait.
So that teleported me further, but it wasn't the right direction.
And now I should be over here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Look, left.
Wait, wait, wait, where am I now?
I'm not entirely convinced yet.
Hold on.
If the teleportation is over here on the right somewhere, then I know what's happening.
It's gotta be over here.
But maybe it's a varying distance.
Wait, why is there so much of this now?
I feel like that was only a little bit before.
I'm losing my mind.
Okay, I think I may have understood what's happening there.
So that's the difference.
I wonder... Okay, I gotta try that with unstable next.
In fact, don't I have that?
No, I don't have it.
Okay, so we gotta try that with unstable.
I gotta get to the bottom of this at some point.
Because there is obviously a difference between the two.
And that may even be the difference.
So this is concentrated mana, right?
So I'm not done exploring here.
I want to find more hearts.
Oh, I need water!
Good thing there's water here.
Is there an enemy in here?
No.
Don't!
That's for you!
He totally died from that.
Pro MLG moves right there.
Holy crap!
Water myself.
I actually got him with that maneuver there.
That's fantastic.
A wand for me!
Am I crazy or did I have the exact same wand?
Before.
I kind of want this instead of that.
This seems kind of cr- Oh, heavy spread.
No.
That is always being applied first.
There's a sniper.
There he is.
I still have the teleport, right?
I do.
Nice.
Very nice.
That's very technical.
Nobody's gonna get that reference.
If you do, you're a god.
And I respect you.
Get him.
Whoa, right.
I have to remember, they bleed teleportation now.
Kind of a big deal.
But I guess I have an easy access to get some teleportation if I need to.
Speaking of...
There are things I want to try with teleportation still.
And it would be nice to get some in a bottle.
Let me get rid of concentrated mana.
I don't think I want concentrated.
Also, what's in here?
The hook bolt.
We can encourage electricity.
This was like a teleport, but not quite the same.
It's a little bit different.
Hey, do you want some of this, buddy?
I'm so slippery.
I guess I could just drink it.
Yeah, that's easier.
Now give me some of... Oh, there's actually not that much down here.
Oh yeah, right, of course.
I guess picking it up is a little bit dangerous.
More concentrated...
Concentrated mana.
What's with all these hands?
Something going on there.
Ooh, berserkium.
Okay, so there's a bunch of teleportation there.
But I can't really pick it up.
I mean, I'll try.
Quick!
I did get a bit of it.
Now I'm kind of stuck in here.
Take me out.
Yeah, look at... I can control it.
Oh yeah!
Take me... Oh wait, it doesn't affect me anymore?
Wait, what?
I'm so confused.
I get so disoriented from that.
It's up here, isn't it?
Oh, hello, guys.
Don't shoot me.
2200 monies.
That's not bad.
Holy fucking Jesus Christ.
That's a lot of crap.
And I think I like it.
I'm sorry, buddy, but I'm replacing you.
That seems way too good.
What's in here, though?
Oh, I really want that.
Maybe I want it more than this.
Yeah.
Yeah, that seems really nice.
Let me make sure I have the right one.
Let's go.
Proper digging, finally.
And a fireball thrower.
Yeah, I don't know.
I really loved that one once.
But nowadays, not so much.
I used to rock that on a glowing lance and it was the best thing ever.
But that was back when I was but a small noob.
I mean, I'm still a noob, but I was more so a noob.
Let's just say that.
OK, well, I think it's time to leave.
Get the hell out of here.
Whoa, imagine if that killed me.
I wonder if it is able to with enough force.
Let's go.
Immediately an explosion in the distance.
Always a nice sign.
At mana and boomerang.
That's lovely stuff.
What's this?
Vacuum field, that's right.
Oh, oh, that one is super good.
Oh, but that one is also super good, but no, I want this.
Hand it over.
Now look at this.
There's all kinds of stuff in here.
All the goodies.
It's like a picket mix, except it was someone else you picked up on the street.
Picked it for you and mixed it for you, and then you paid.
Linear arc.
This adds five damage, by the way.
So this goes in here.
Acid, and reduce spread.
We can reduce spread even more.
Actually, there's not that many cool things on here.
I expected more crazy stuff.
But now that we have add mana, I mean, the worlds are oyster here.
I mean, come on.
It's gonna be wild.
What is this even for?
Hold on.
Cast three spells ahead above and below the caster.
That seems horrible.
Why not just use this?
Yeah, I don't get it.
Above and below.
Yeah.
I don't want that.
Lightning bolt?
No.
But I'll keep it for now.
There.
I guess I could also use a magic arrow with trigger.
That seems nice.
The rest I don't really care for that much.
Yeah, get rid of that one, that one, that one, that one.
This one may even be... Oh, wait, it actually cast something.
Oh, I didn't see that.
Fuck, I was trying to make a wand with that now because of all the slots.
Hold up, what is it casting?
What is this?
Fly upwards?
Causes a projectile to aim straight upwards a short time.
No.
Oh, but it sucks anyway.
But that could be fixed with add mana, I guess.
But whatever.
It is what it is.
Okay, so let's see what we can do.
There's this one.
That is ideal for mining.
146.
What?
Oh, is that... Wait, why does it do more damage sometimes?
So these statues are bugged, by the way.
People told me that, so I can't really count on what they're telling me.
That is very unfortunate.
Add mana is not really needed unless we can find out a way to brrrr this wand.
You know?
And I feel like I'm at the cusp of getting back to the way I did it once where I made it work.
Let me get rid of that one and this one.
Put it here for now.
Also, we can make a digging wand now.
That one sucks though, so maybe we put it on here instead.
Not bad.
What if we add...
What is the issue?
Recharge time.
But look at this.
This is the thing that's weirding me out.
See, that's definitely faster.
Isn't it?
Hold on.
Bum-bum.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, that's... Oh, the mana is horrendous!
Yikes!
Didn't even see that.
Oh, but I guess we have digging bolt we can use.
That costs no mana.
Which is insane.
Like look, this totally affects it.
Why is there so much recoil?
I guess I am reducing recharge time a lot there.
In any case, maybe I want to put this in here instead.
Because then we have this one.
Where is it?
Give me the extra damage.
Where did I put it?
Ah, here.
Utilize this.
Inside of there.
And I guess we can just do this one.
Because this one already takes five mana.
This costs one mana.
And then inside of here we put some extra goodies.
Like that's already good damage right there.
That's good damage.
Oh, hello.
Welcome to my abode.
Make yourself at home, huh?
Yeah, I am not going to need this yet.
I could use this on my digging wand I guess.
Some... some... one of the digging wands at least.
I think I am happy with this right now.
But let me see the spells again.
It's also these guys.
What about a lightning bolt at the end?
Maybe a bit too crazy.
What if we do this?
Nah, I don't want that, I don't want that, I don't want that.
Oh, we have to remember, this one also increases damage.
So I am getting extra damage from that as well.
This is getting to be really cool.
There.
That is solid.
It's just a little slow, but I mean look at the mana we use.
It's totally okay.
That's a good balance there.
And now we can do a digging bolt, or even the energy sphere, or energy orb.
Yeah, which one is best for that?
Maybe that one.
Even though 0.85 recharge time, it's really bad.
Yeah, look at the recharge, but then we add this.
It's a little better.
It's not quite there.
It's not quite there either.
No, that's not gonna cut it.
This one may be an okay digging wand.
I mean, we don't care about it going upwards after a while, if it's a digging wand.
We don't give a shit.
Oh yeah, there it is!
Made it!
Yeah, that was what it took.
Look at that, there's even a shit ton of recoil on it.
All right.
The digging has been achieved.
I'm gonna leave one up there.
These can go here.
Oh, it would be cool to put one of them in here, wouldn't it?
That's 11 damage plus four explosive.
And that would make it dig as well.
Five... oh, that looks really good.
This is more damage though, I think.
But this is really cool though.
Isn't it?
Maybe a bit dangerous.
The good news is, I'm not gonna be producing blood from everyone all the time.
Which means, if there's an uku, he's not gonna be bleeding teleportation too much.
Which may be better for me.
So I think I like it.
Yeah.
And we're gonna save this at mana until we really need it.
What if I put an extra one here?
I'm not gonna change anything.
Pretty much the same.
Actually, there's a bit of difference.
The mana gets used quicker here.
So that indicates to me that it is doing it faster.
Yeah.
Put it here.
The question is, should I put my teleport here or there?
That's a long recharge time.
So maybe it is better on that one.
Although it does recharge very slow.
Alright, this is actually fine.
Yeah.
Then we throw this one away.
That seems good to me.
Alright, let's get the... let's get a move on.
Oh, we could also do explosion at the end.
Oh, that's 80 mana though.
But with mana... add mana, that's only... what is that?
50 mana extra, but that's still a lot of mana extra.
But it's there.
We can think about it.
Let me see the other spells real quick before I leave.
Yo, what if we do this?
Here.
What is that gonna look like?
Oh, wait, wait.
That is gonna absorb my own spells.
Oh, that's interesting.
I don't think I like that.
No, no, no, no.
Do that.
Okay, so I may actually have enough to kill Stuart here.
I think I can do it.
I have the power.
Let me think, worst case.
I don't have my tablet.
Dude!
Watch this.
Hold on.
No!
Okay.
That's it.
And we have enough to get back in.
It's a little bit risky.
I mean, but it's fine.
It works.
What if I couldn't dig here?
That would be a disaster.
Dude, there's so much recall on this, I can't actually dig.
It's gotta be the always cast spell that's doing that.
The digging sucks on this wand.
Because look, my character stands still while digging.
I'm holding A right now.
Oh no, the digging wand sucks.
Terrible.
That went straight through this guy.
Wait, what's going on?
I think the linear arc is messing with it.
Something's happening here.
There's something going on for sure that's not supposed to happen.
This is a really scuffed setup.
Yeah, no, no, no.
We're going back in.
Let me see if I can do this.
Holy shit.
I am in control of teleportation.
The master.
Also, give me one of these.
Throw this here.
So yeah, that's not gonna work, unfortunately.
This is point fives, but this is the one with the very low manage.
Ah, damn it.
This is terrible.
I guess I'll use this instead.
Look how slow it is.
I don't have a good way of digging.
Huh.
Ah, that's frustrating.
I mean, that works.
Actually, it's not that bad.
This can work in a pinch.
Yeah, it's not that bad.
It's okay.
And then in this one, we need to... there's something going on there that I don't...
I think it may be the speed up.
Maybe that's doing something.
So extra damage to a triplicate bolt.
And then we add something else in there.
Such as, maybe just some sparks.
Spark bolts.
And then instead of that, we do this.
And we add another spark bolt, if I have it.
Or this one.
Yeah.
It's a little bit fucked up, but...
Oh, no, I'm empty.
No more teleportation.
Yikes.
How do I...
Okay, I'm gonna try and fight this guy.
Worst case, I can teleport out.
You know, it's not the end of the world.
I'm just gonna... yeah.
Yeah, that's the plan.
That is the plan.
Get rid of that one.
This one I will replace.
Alright, Stuart.
Let's have a good old fight.
Dude, my heart drops every time I hear that sound.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I have to remember, I have a heal, I have a heal.
Hey!
That wasn't too bad!
Fuck yeah!
I don't know why I was so afraid.
But, we still gotta make our way out of here.
I guess we can do that with this.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
Very nice.
But I have to remember, Stuart is gonna be there for every mountain now.
Oh, goodness.
The recoil!
Oh, the mana recharge is painful, look at that.
Let's just wait a bit.
Oh, wait, I can teleport through that.
I just wanna make it comfortable.
Oh, that works.
Nice!
Very nice.
And go back to what we had before.
There.
What did I have on this wand?
Oh, this...
Wait, there's still re...
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait a second, is that what's doing this?
Why do I have so much recoil?
Look.
I think it may be this.
I think this perk is making me have recoil.
Like, this is a normal digging wand, and look at this.
I can float with it.
That's how much recoil there is.
It's gotta be that one.
Dang.
Alright, so I guess in this case, it may be better to do this.
Even the mana recharge.
But then we add this.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hey!
There it is.
I guess we don't need it to be that fast.
This is more than plenty.
I guess we can make it a little faster.
So the digging bolt is producing a lot of recoil, huh?
That's very interesting.
I like it.
Let's just rock like... No, I do want the extra.
What am I looking for?
That one.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
Okay, not bad, not bad.
Teleport, damage, go!
Very cool.
The only issue is, I'm not able to cut through metal.
That's okay.
Oh, no!
It was a friendo!
It's okay.
I'll find another friend.
Oh, I gotta blow that up.
In fact, a friend is very welcome right now.
Because I have low HP, and I don't want to take that heart just yet.
I'm that greedy, okay?
I'm a greedy boy.
If you remember, it's an R.
R, R, R, okay.
And that's Q.
Ouch.
Dude, I one shot these guys.
Yo, that's...
really good.
There we go.
That's the one I needed.
That's really solid.
Boink.
Let me see if there's recoil on this as well, the same way.
There should be.
Not as much!
Is it these?
Why is that faster?
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
That's the dig right there.
That's the dig.
Beautiful.
We have done it.
No, I want to keep one of these teleports, actually.
Because if I end up throwing this wand away, because I find a really good one, I want to be able to have another teleport.
But that is a solid digging wand.
Very nice.
We could even add this...
to make it able to dig through the big stuff.
It still digs kind of slow, though, because I'm still pushing through like that.
I don't like that.
I may have to go with this.
Yeah.
The recoil is pretty annoying.
I don't need two of these.
Yeah, that's good.
Why is this not slower or faster?
Anyway, we saved the ad mana here.
That's a win in my book.
It's not as fast, but that's fine.
We don't need faster than that.
We do not...
Like,
I one-shot the mechanical enemies here.
That's how good this wand is.
It's crazy.
It's very high damage output in one shot.
That makes it really good, I guess, against...
Yalchemisti.
Because he lets up his shield when he takes damage, right?
So if I get a lot of damage in before he has a chance...
to let up his shield, that's when I'll be rocking his world.
Think about it.
He has a wahun!
Always so scared of people with...
Yes, sir.
I will take that off your hands.
Don't mind if I do.
So now we gotta go back again.
Immediately.
I gotta be careful here.
How much damage is it?
Oh, but hold on, hold on, hold on.
This adds extra damage, right?
That makes it a little bit risky.
I have an idea, though.
I have a great idea.
And we gotta make it come back.
But watch this.
Boomerang!
The boomerang!
How perfect is that?
Huh?
Tell me, that's the most perfect thing ever.
Now, how do I make it so that it only shoots...
Dude, by the way, this wand is not bad.
This is a wand!
An actual wand.
Hold up.
Oh, there's also this one here.
Thanks.
Oh man, things are getting exciting.
Oh yeah.
Hold up now.
Give me one of these, please.
Let me just see.
So, I need to be careful.
This may do more damage than I think, at first.
So, I'm actually gonna heal.
Just to be safe here.
I need to see how much damage I take.
Oh, so it's... okay.
Did I get hit?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh.
I need to activate friendly fire.
Uh, what do I have for that?
Can I do that?
Hmm.
Not right here.
Poison arc.
No, there's nothing on the floor.
Alright, well.
Rip.
We gotta find something that will, uh...
make it damage us.
Okay.
We can do that.
So, that means we don't have to utilize this in the immediate moment.
That's actually okay.
I hate that I don't have space.
Maybe leave this here.
Teleport there.
This stays like that.
Now, this one down here is actually legit.
Let's see if we can't make something happen now, huh?
With all of these slots...
Come on.
Something's gotta happen.
Like, look, it's almost faster than this one up here, which makes no sense.
How is that even... real?
Whoops.
Now it's slower.
Now it's faster.
Huh?
Bro.
One, two, three, four, five.
Right.
Okay.
And
then...
I...
I'm actually going nuts over this.
Like...
Hold up.
Let me think.
What if I just replace everything with these...
What am I limited by?
Castelae.
It's castelae.
That damn castelae.
That adds castelae.
Now this one is the one!
How can I make this impact everything?
Is there a way?
That one does nothing for me.
Maybe it's the formation pentagon that's messing with me here.
In some way, maybe it's doing something undesirable.
So now there's three spells.
One, two, three.
Okay.
And that's the speed we're operating at here.
Gotcha.
I think I can put this in here safely as well.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
Uhh...
Why is this so...
Okay.
I get the issue.
We don't have...
We have very high castelae, right?
Because we don't have the recharge bar popping up on the right there.
It's not popping.
So I'm thinking it's gotta be the luminous drill that we somehow add into this mix.
But I've tried every position.
It doesn't even affect the speed.
Like, it does nothing.
Which is so odd to me.
Or maybe it does.
Hold up.
Let me see the board.
Okay, I think it does actually...
Yeah, okay, I understand.
I understand what's happening now.
I just don't remember how I...
How the fucking hell I managed to make this shoot fast the other time.
That's the thing I don't get.
So what's happening here?
The luminous drill does reduce castelae.
It does reduce recharge time.
But only in the period after this spell is being shot and the next one appears.
There is still a castelae of .33 and anything being modified in here.
And a recharge timer of .22 after this section of spells has been shot.
That's what's happening.
Because you see how fast the luminous drill appears?
And then the other one appears right after?
That's basically saying that this is being shot.
And then immediately afterwards, this is being shot.
So these stats are affecting it, but only in the little period between when this ends and this whole block starts, if that makes sense.
So I understand that.
I just don't understand how I once managed to make this work.
The way I'm trying to make it work.
You know?
That's like the big problem here.
Honestly, I think maybe I just had a quick recharge and that is the solution to everything.
I just had a quick recharge.
I just don't remember more than that.
I can add speed to this as well, because why not?
That's pretty cool.
And now we can add more things.
Let me add this one there.
In fact, we can go a little nuts here.
We can make this...
We don't need to shoot fast if anything we hit dies in one hit anyway, right?
So I'm thinking five spells.
Or no, I'm thinking three spells, which is one, two, three.
The third one is going to be the pentagon.
It's going to be wild.
The pentagon with...
another one of these.
That's two.
We need three more.
Damn.
Maybe a digging bolt.
And what else?
I don't even know.
Maybe that one.
Why not throw it in there?
And then we add one more thing.
Maybe a spitter bolt.
Why not?
Look at that shit.
It's... damn.
That's a lot of damage.
I need to test that.
How much damage?
Oh, it's not even that much.
Okay, it is that much.
Oh, it's a lot.
Yeah, that's great.
Dude, Yalki Misty had like, what is it?
A thousand HP or something?
Or 800?
That's what I do now.
Unless he somehow gets less damage from some of these types.
Who knows?
But that seems pretty damn crazy at this point.
That's a good amount of damage.
I'm gonna leave these deadly heals here.
No, I'm not.
I'm taking them.
Yeah, I'm taking them with me.
Because if I find something that will allow me to make these...
Actually deadly to me, even though the name says deadly.
What a scam, by the way.
Oh, hold on.
I can make this even better.
That should be even more damage.
That's nice.
Oh, but the question is...
695.
What if I put this outside of this?
Oh, I think it's better.
Oh my goodness.
Makes it even better.
Unless... No, actually, hold on.
Is it changing anything?
No, it's the same.
Okay, never mind.
I guess this one counts as a spell inside of here, so it's being applied along with everything else.
And this spell contains all of this crap.
What a mess.
This is 8 damages.
You know what?
This is better.
I kind of want to put something more crazy.
I want to put an explosion in there.
But it's a little bit insane, I guess.
If I don't have explosion resistance...
Yeah, let's not do that.
Let's not go too crazy.
Death Cross, though.
Why don't we try that?
Let's see.
That's 80 mana.
Oh wait, that's...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's way too scary.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
I don't like that at all.
What did I have before?
I
don't remember.
Oh yeah, one of these.
Leave this here.
All right, let's go.
Okay, we have a beefed up wand now.
It's a one-hit wonder.
But it's slow as hell.
But that's okay.
No, it was a friendo!
I was too fast on the trigger finger there.
Shit, I forgot to make my digging wand.
Oh wait, does this dig... does this dig okay?
It's actually fine.
And that frees up another slot.
Oh yeah.
Oof, lovely.
This is more like a fucking 50-caliber...
sniper here.
Like, it kills anything it touches.
And I like that, actually.
Wait, why am I taking damage?
Do I have something that damages me here?
Maybe.
Dude, what I really need now is...
bloodlust.
That's the thing I need.
There we go, okay.
Nah.
I just had to jump up into that.
Like an idiot.
Oh, there's a friend!
Let's keep him alive.
Hey, friendo!
I have a little potion for you.
Come here.
No, no, no.
Heal me.
Yes!
Amazing!
Nice!
Come with me.
We are going on adventures.
You and me, buddy.
His name is Daniel.
Say hi to Daniel.
No, Daniel!
No!
Daniel!
That's so sad.
Didn't even get to know him very well.
We're going to have a barbecue and everything.
Wait, I think I tried that one.
Oh, what the hell?
Where did you guys come from?
Boink.
Bro, this one is fun.
I don't even care about it.
I think I'm too obsessed with the idea of making a machine gun.
I don't need to.
This is perfectly fine.
This is fun, man.
I click and things die.
How is that not good?
Oh, you know what?
Actually, for instances where they have a shield that you need to get through, it may not be the greatest.
Although he did die, so...
Oh, but wait a minute!
I wonder, because there are so many spells in quick succession here, I wonder if that actually does not immediately remove one of those barriers and then the next spells are going to hit immediately after.
Huh?
We got a test.
Lava to blood!
I'll buy that.
I'll buy that too.
Aiming arc.
No.
Mist of spirits.
Hmm.
Nope.
I do kind of want to buy aiming arc.
No, I don't.
Also, wait, wait.
This is it.
I've got to be careful here, though.
Here we are.
Yeah, I'm coming back for you.
Oh, actually, no, I'm not.
I'm going to try something here.
What happens now?
Nothing.
Okay.
I'll be back.
I need to acquire other materials to test.
But I want to test the teleportation for sure.
That is like the obvious one.
Given the eye and all that.
Guys, come here.
Wait, does it actually penetrate them?
I feel like I killed more than once sometimes.
But maybe that's the explosive effect of some of these.
Very nice.
Measure.
Wait, how did he die?
I missed.
Some of the projectiles must have hit him after.
Yeah, probably what happened.
Oh, my God, there's so much blood.
I actually kind of like the idea of having a damaged one that also does the digging.
Because that frees up an entire one slot.
Maybe that's something I should experiment more with.
This is actually really freeing.
Okay, that's a sick one, but blood mist?
What is the point of that?
I'll take it because I don't have anything else.
Here.
Why not?
Let's hang on to the blood mist.
Till we find something else.
So it says 126 on them, or like 28 or whatever.
This does way more than that.
I don't know why it only says that I do that little damage.
Unless it's because they die, and it only records as much damage as the health they have.
Uh oh, hold on, it's a friend.
It's a friend, but let me kill the other guy first.
Hey, come here, it's just you and me now.
Daniel the second.
Let me douse you in this magical liquid.
The dousing has begun.
Wait.
Yeah, it is pheromone.
Hey!
Oh, there we go.
I need to pour it right on his head.
That's the difference here.
Okay.
Follow me.
Don't go in there.
Don't go up there.
I'm clearing the way.
Oh, I thought that was a turret.
Oh, thank you, man.
Thank you.
Stay back, stay back.
You...
I told you not...
Motherfucker.
Daniel the second's rip.
His time wasn't very long.
But he did heal me up.
So, here's that.
Wow.
Oh, friendos!
I didn't mean to kill him, but okay.
There's another one.
Oh, no.
Did he die as well?
Man, I'm taking a lot of damage here.
Also, my ear is itchy.
Hey, guys!
Report right on your head.
Man, I'm running out of the...
Guys, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Heal me.
Yes!
Nice!
This is so sick, by the way.
What a discovery I made with that, huh?
So glad I tried that.
And it's been a while since I did it, too.
Shit!
How come I can hit them?
I thought, no friendly fire.
Okay.
I need fire immunity.
The bomb cards.
Look at the manamax.
1,500, though.
Makes it up good.
You know, I'm going to grab some more water.
May as well do it.
Am I crazy, or do these guys not emit as much oil and fire anymore?
I wonder if it's because of my setup here.
Sometimes when I kill them, they immediately emit a shit ton of oil and fire.
But not this time around.
Ow!
Come here.
Where's the sniper?
Oish!
You little piece of shit.
Did he die?
Where are you?
There you are.
How much damage I do.
It's fantastic.
I feel like, okay, despite all the suffering earlier from trying to make the wand that I had in mind, I feel like in the process I've discovered a new way to wake wands.
Like the slower, but way more damage wands.
The friendo was a Beidou.
No, Daniel!
Drink this liquid.
No!
Yes!
Oh, yeah, that's the spot.
That's the spot.
A little higher, a little higher.
There it is.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
Yo, what the hell is that?
Explosion on drunk enemies.
It looks like a tree.
Very cool design.
Makes the projectile explode upon collision with creatures covered in alcohol, which is almost never.
So I guess this almost never happens.
So that's nice.
I'll take it.
That's a special-ass wand right there.
Don't die now.
Stay away, stay away.
Okay, there we go.
Your friends are up there.
Keep healing me.
A lot of digging bolts.
Don't think I want it.
Another friendo.
But I don't have much pheromone left.
I need to find more.
He's not my friend anymore over there.
He has turned sides again.
He's a two-faced bastard.
Don't fall on the ice!
Careful.
Okay.
Whoa!
Ouch.
If he follows me in here, he dies.
Yeah.
Classic Daniel move.
Something I never would do.
Daniel, though, in a heartbeat.
Look at that gang over there.
Uh-oh.
Why is it electrified?
Where are all these enemies coming from?
Uh-oh.
Oh,
I'm definitely going to put an explosion at the end of this one.
But I need to find explosion immunity.
And then I'm going to do so much damage.
I would like to acquire some small teleport.
And not the big variation.
I can't get through here.
Can I?
He had a wand as well.
An Eldritch Portal.
No, thanks.
No.
I went through lots of combination of spells in my head there.
None of them made sense right now.
Whoops.
Aha!
At chests?
Don't mind if I do.
Homebringer.
I would not like that.
I shall say no to that.
Maybe this wand will please me.
Hmm.
That's the thing I haven't understood yet.
And this wand is not bad.
Would you look at the mana chart speed and the castelay on that?
Whoa.
I may actually just take it.
That seems super good.
I can probably make something neat out of that.
I don't want to go that way.
Whoops.
I think my time here is done in this level.
I'm going to slowly head for the exit.
But still kill things on the way, you know.
And then I think I'm ready to pay Stuart a wizard.
Oh, he has a big what the fuck that looks like a dick.
Look at that.
Wow.
His greed sickens me.
He doesn't need this many Homebringer teleport bolts.
Did he also have a wand?
Oh, here we go.
I have a bit of pheromone left.
No, Daniel.
Come here.
Stand in this for me.
Mush, mush, mush, mush, mush, mush.
No, come here.
Dang it.
No,
wait, I have an idea.
Daniel, come here.
Maybe I can lure him into this pheromone pit.
Come here.
Now I go down and stay right below it.
Come on.
No, no, no, no, he's too smart.
Clever girl.
Daniel too clever for this world.
Okay.
Let's get out of here.
Oh, I forgot about him.
That's okay.
Three empty bottles.
It's rare you see that.
Very rare.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Bite, bite, bite.
Shit, we don't have time.
No time.
Just kill him.
Oh yeah, easy, easy, easy.
No props at all.
Now watch.
This will blow your mind.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, wait.
I promise I'll blow your mind.
Come on.
Blow their minds.
Okay.
Maybe not so much.
Okay, you know what?
That's better.
That's better, I guess.
What do we got?
Ooh.
Gas fire.
No.
Ooh.
This one is good, guys.
I will take this.
Fire immunity?
You can't say no to that.
Now this thing right here.
Imbuse the projectile with a curse that makes the target hit by the projectile to waste away.
I am... because I don't know exactly how that works, I think the best way to find out is to just put it on a wand that I use all the time.
So how about we just put it in here?
See what happens.
Something's bound to happen.
I'm gonna notice something at some point.
Maybe.
That explodes into a sticky mess.
This one could be a nice thing to have.
Yeah.
Why don't we just do this?
And then add some... I don't even know.
Why is that so slow?
There we go, there we go.
Like that's gonna... that's a surefire way to get rid of long.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
Imagine having that, by the way, and vampirism.
Oof.
That would be sick.
That would be humongous.
Now, do I have any way to damage myself here?
Anti-gravity.
Freeze?
Oh, that's a...
explosion.
Hmm.
The explosion...
is 68 damage.
I feel like I gotta try this.
Wait, wha...
Wait a minute.
One, two, three...
Hmm.
Why is nothing happening?
Hold up.
Oh, wait a minute.
Do I not have enough mana?
You know what?
That's probably what that is.
Yeah.
Because it's never being shot.
Interesting.
Okay.
Alright.
Is that what I had before?
I don't remember.
Fuck.
Didn't I also have some of the big balls?
Big, big, big the ball.
Let me see the DPS.
Wait, what?
Oh.
Oh, look!
It's taking damage!
Dude, that's... that's crazy amount of damage.
That is not bad at all!
Hello?
Especially on a boss...
where you have downtime, where you can't attack, just have some damage...
happen.
Right?
That seems kinda nuts.
Very cool.
Now...
I think I had this over here before.
Not that it matters much, I think.
Maybe it does matter much.
Is that more damage?
Wait a minute.
Is it ticking for more damage?
The more damage I do.
Ooh.
Weird.
Anyway.
Yeah, that's interesting.
Okay.
I think I like it the way it is.
Yep.
But I feel like it's nice to have all kinds of different damage types.
Like that, you know, just have a bunch of different stuff in here.
The reason is...
So this is some explosive damage.
This is damage slice, and then you can have some third damage, you know?
So you get a good mix of everything.
So depending on the enemy, it's like whatever.
You know?
We already have some explosive damage, maybe we add that.
Just to switch it up a bit, you know?
Just to have a happy little...
switch it up situation.
Okay, so...
Stuart is dead.
That means we can just make our way out of here.
That's gonna take forever.
What did I do before?
So why is that there?
Dude, maybe I used two of these.
Actually, I like that.
Wait, am I running out of mana?
Oh, I think I am.
Yeah, now I'm not.
I see.
It's actually easy to see.
Like when the bar goes red, it means you don't have enough mana.
Uh-huh.
But I could add and add mana, I guess.
But then this one wouldn't work.
Yeah, that's way too slow.
That's better.
Alright.
Throw this away.
I can make this faster.
There we go.
Dig it!
Technically, we don't need more than a little bit of a sliver here for the teleport, but I'm gonna make it nice and open just for convenience sake.
There we go.
And we should be able to easily fit through that.
Lovely stuff.
This one right here, I could just leave here, I guess, until I find something.
Yeah.
The rest stays with me.
Yeah, that seems good.
Actually, I don't need this because the digging is already on this one.
So I'm gonna leave these here as well.
And let's leave the boomerang.
No, keep the boomerang.
Leave the double here.
Put this one up here and that one there.
That's it.
Let's-a go!
The jungle!
I have arrived.
The hair in the back of your neck stands up.
I mean, always, when there are spiders involved.
Dude, things really do die fast.
Even these little fuckhead spiders that always take so many shots, they just die here.
It's lovely.
I was hating on my wand, but now I love it.
Oh yeah, and I'm immune to fire.
Oh, that is just fantastic.
I love recent developments here.
Very happy with how things are going now.
Hold up a second.
If a valid target appears somewhere in the proximity of a projectile, the projectile will teleport.
Wait, what?
Oh, I see, quadruple.
Oh, that was actually a little bit sketchy what I just did.
I forgot about this.
I could have killed myself.
That was scary.
You know what saved me here?
Concentrated spells.
Because I would have shot it in each direction here and killed myself for sure.
Holy crap.
So I should be okay shooting this now.
Dude, that's sick.
That is a cool ass wand.
We got to find more hearts.
We are at a very low max HP, I feel like.
This is just not acceptable.
The max HP is too damn low.
Oh, that's how that meme goes.
Except it's usually high.
Wait, the lag?
No, that's it.
I'm done.
Dude, I'm tempted to go to the ancient laboratory immediately.
It's that crazy.
But I guess it's difficult, because I don't really have a proper digging method to get up there.
I have luminous drill.
Maybe I can finagle my way into having a really fast luminous drill.
But it's going to be a bit of a pain.
And I still have things to kill here and stuff, you know?
And I have very low HP.
I'm scared of that, boss.
You will probably fuck me up if I'm not careful.
I
won't.
Okay.
There's a mage.
You know what this wand is really good against?
The mage is where we switch places.
Because I'm instantly going to kill him.
Ah, fuck.
But now I can control it.
I wonder, can I...
Can I destroy the Uproskivi?
Like, let's say I have a luminous drill.
Can I just drill that shit out of existence?
Or black hole it out of existence?
That is maybe the best way to dispose of that crap.
I'm also really curious to see how much damage I'm going to do against the big spiders.
With my current setup.
Imagine if I could one-shot those guys.
That would be fucking crazy.
Ah, I knew that was going to happen.
Yeah, I saw that one coming.
Damn it all.
At heart.
Although light is nice to have.
Stay in the blood.
It's worm pheromone.
I really have to keep an eye out on the outside here, where I live.
If it starts to rain, I need to ASAP get out there and remove my clothes that are hanging.
It does look a little grey outside right now, I'm worried.
But I have faith.
Oh my god!
Look at this!
Someone has been hard at work.
Maybe I should have just let him be.
Oh no, he can... Why did I kill him?
He was so hard at work, like a good boy.
Dang it.
I should have thought that through.
That could have been my ticket back.
In fact, as time goes on here, I'm not that scared about these spiders anymore.
Very nice.
Whoa.
Wait, a green projectile?
What does that do?
Maybe I don't want to find out.
Also, this guy didn't die from my shot.
Okay, so that's the twitchy one.
Gotcha.
Actually, the projectile colors are quite informative here.
What?
What's happening?
Uh...
Huh?
What just happened?
Okay, I'm going back to heal.
I have no idea what just happened.
I'm scared.
Ah, don't go that way.
What the hell?
Why did I take damage?
I need to reevaluate.
Okay, we're safe.
Uh, what just happened there?
Did I get hit by my own with this?
I wonder.
That's the only change I can think about.
There's nothing else that I changed here.
Kind of want to test it, but I'm not so sure.
I was taking damage like boop, boop, boop, boop, you know?
So, makes me think that was the same effect.
I don't think I like that.
Now I kind of want to remove it.
But I'm not sure if that's actually what's causing it, or if it was some kind of enemy who did something to me.
Come on, spiders.
All right, dude, I'm going straight into Loki lair here.
I have no fear.
Watch.
I'm going in.
Wait, we're not in the Loki lair.
Not yet.
Well, we got some people from behind here that want to join the party.
Dude, the fact that I one shot these guys is crazy.
Hold on, poison!
Shit!
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
Poison is the worst.
And I got to remember, I can't take damage from fire.
Oh, yeah.
Come on, Loki lair.
The hell is that?
A giant flower.
Oh, you know what?
I will take some blood.
I need this.
Yes.
Hand over the blood.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, no.
It doesn't die.
It heals again.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, wait, it died.
These guys are a mystery.
It's really odd.
Now, that is my dream.
I love this.
Hold on, how many do I have left of these?
Six, eight, okay.
Let me try it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You want some?
Come here.
How do you like them apples?
Oh, you love them?
You love apples.
That's bad news for me.
True orbit.
I can...
What do you mean?
Why true orbit?
Why not just orbit?
I guess it does add three damage.
That's actually kind of a nice thing.
But this one is just...
No, it only has four slots.
It's not actually that great.
No, I need to let go of that one.
I don't know why I was so obsessed with it.
It's not that good.
Okay, I'm not going in the Loki lair.
I've changed my mind.
I cannot kill the big spiders fast enough.
I'm not going.
By the way, my theory on that...
is that...
they heal...
from...
projectile damage.
Oh, look!
Wasting away.
Maybe I shoot him once.
He wastes away.
I'm going to try this again.
Come here.
That does nothing to him.
I mean, he does die eventually, I think.
Oh, he died there.
I wonder if he died there because of the...
wasting away effect.
Because I didn't damage him just now.
So he must have died from that.
That's what I'm thinking.
I see you up there.
Okay, portal here.
I need more hearts.
Do I still have my luminous drill?
I do.
That's good.
I'm rich.
I'm going to have so much money for the next holy mountain.
Oh, what the hell is going on here?
Nope!
Makes it.
Makes it up good.
That can mix for a while.
Look at this place!
This is actually really cool.
Looks like some kind of overgrown...
post-apocalyptic bunker or something.
Giant firebolt and plasma beam in hand.
I don't know.
I don't want that right now.
But thanks for asking, game.
I really appreciate that.
Aha!
Nice.
That's what I was looking for.
Oh!
Eh?
Oh no.
Where are you?
Ouch!
He keeps hitting me with that.
Asshole!
There's one more somewhere.
Show yourself.
I need to heal.
I feel like I'm very low HP for the stage of the game.
I need more.
Alright, let's just go.
Let's see what damage we can get up to here.
Or trouble!
That's the expression.
Okay.
Let's do it!
Ah!
Ooh!
That hurt.
Ah!
He died from the wasting away.
100%.
Plague rats.
No, I hate all of these.
Reroll that.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you for that.
That's lovely.
That is lovely, that.
And we have implicate spell.
What does this do again?
I have to remind myself.
Quantum split circle of oil.
Blood cloud.
The double trigger.
I'll take that.
I would like a double trigger.
I'm also gonna take...
that one.
I'm experimenting here.
Maybe I leave...
Where'd you come from?
Fucking asshole!
Spreading teleportation here now.
How did you get in?
There's gotta be a hole.
I guess he teleported in.
Dammit!
That's really annoying.
I will forgo...
Honestly, that one.
I have...
Wait!
I forgot my...
Shit.
I forgot my old...
wand, so I'm actually gonna keep it.
Let's get rid of the explosion.
What does this do again?
Cast a copy of a projectile behind you, but the copy...
still cost mana.
Copy!
Hold on, I think I tested something like this before, but not with this.
What is something... that one?
Oh, behind me?
Let's not do that one, then.
I need to test whether or not I can do something crazy here.
I guess just...
Fuck, I don't know.
I don't know.
Sure, this one.
Why not?
Don't die now.
Okay, but hold on.
Fuck!
Whatever.
It's fine.
Ah, now I have more of him.
Fucking annoying.
Okay.
All right, well, I have to try.
Unfortunately, there's no infinite spells there.
What else can I try?
All right, this one.
So, ten explosive damage.
I want to try and throw this in here instead.
Why not, right?
That seems cool.
Just have a bit of that in there.
Oh, let's not hit that stuff.
What else could I... What is this one again?
Quantum thingy.
Makes a projectile split into three projectiles, whose existences are entangled.
All right.
Why don't we try to throw that on here?
Maybe instead of that.
Yeah.
No, maybe instead of...
No, that's fine.
Wait, what did I replace?
That one, right?
Yeah.
Oh, hello.
Well, that's... that's...
Oh, I don't even have mana for that, never mind.
Wait, why don't I...
Why don't I have mana for that?
Are you kidding?
Oh, this one cost 65.
Holy shit.
That's why.
That's actually worse.
What if I put it here?
It's actually worse.
Yeah, look at that.
It's just straight up.
This is just better.
Like, what?
All right.
Well, I tried.
It was worth an attempt.
Give me that one.
Unless... Oh, I have a bunch here.
Fuck me.
That was stupid.
Let me see the damage now.
Because I feel like these guys are, like, insane.
Oh, I don't have mana for that.
Man, I must be really close.
Must be super close.
Like, the bar goes to, like, here.
How much is that?
60?
Am I at 20?
40?
60?
Something like that.
Very little.
Did it cost 35 mana?
Did it cost 15?
What if I just do this?
Freeze up a little bit.
That's enough.
Oh, yeah, now we're talking.
It's about the same, I guess.
Yeah, it's not that crazy, actually.
And now the damage doesn't show anymore?
Is that because...
Okay, it just sort of stops showing.
All right.
That's fair.
Teleport here.
The true orbit.
Why don't we try to put this on here?
See what happens.
Oh, wow.
It comes back to me.
Oh, that's funny.
What the hell?
That's actually really cool.
It also adds a bunch of time to... Dude!
This is it.
This is the attempt.
No?
Oh, wait, this is not a projectile.
Huh.
Maybe we need to try it more.
Maybe we need to use all of them at once, like in quick succession.
You know?
Interesting.
So I need to see how much damage this does now.
Oh, fuck, I didn't mean to do that.
What if I do that?
That's funny.
Dude, you can make some crazy stuff with this one.
The true orbit is interesting.
Do not touch this.
Oh, yeah, I'm doing insane damage right now.
Wow.
Still don't have enough mana for that.
But I could add and add mana.
And maybe it's enough.
Maybe we don't need the speed.
Although the speed is nice.
Wait, does...
Wow, does it really add that much?
You're fucking kidding me.
Hold up.
Wow, dude, the triple kit...
is nuts.
That's even better.
Isn't it?
Although I feel like I want one of these in here.
Just because...
it has explosive damage on it and maybe that's good.
That's actually worse.
Better.
Hmm.
Yeah, okay.
But I guess the statue is... you can't really rely on it.
It's a bit of a weird one.
Now the portal, put it up here.
I guess I can put all these on here.
I don't need to...
Yeah, that's fine.
This one right here is kind of nuts.
I do actually need this.
I
need a fast one.
I don't really have a fast one.
That's the closest thing.
There's too many goddamn spells and too little room to carry them all.
This is actually a disaster.
You know what, let's take these and replace them here.
With that one.
Seems better.
And then on this one...
Let me just speed that one up.
Gotta find a black hole, man.
I mean, I know where there is one.
It's gotta go grab it.
What is blocking me?
Losing my mind.
What the...
Is it the floor?
Oh, it was.
Okay, okay, I see.
They are very angry with me.
Good thing I don't give a shit.
You can be as angry as you want.
Don't care.
You're gonna be extremely angry at me then?
Nice.
Back to this.
I will leave this one here.
And put this one here.
And all of this, honestly, I don't care about it.
This one can go to hell.
This one can...
Stay.
I guess I could use that as a transport wand for other spells.
If I really need to.
Oh yeah, I'm doing some damage here.
Sick.
So the plan is to find a black hole or something...
I don't know.
Something that digs really effectively.
And then I'm gonna go back up.
And then it's time to face Yalkemisti.
That was bad.
Just lost a lot of HP there.
Yeah, I can't get in there.
Don't have the means.
The digging has been severely lacking in this run.
Holy crap.
Oh, that's acid.
Will you stay still?
Oh.
Ooh, bloodlust.
Now we're talking.
I'm a little bit scared though.
Oh, I don't even have money for it.
Guess I gotta come back.
What's that?
All kinds of nasty materials in there.
I love this wand.
I feel like I'm playing way too aggressive here for my amount of HP and the healing capabilities that I possess.
This is just not good.
I need to calm the fuck down here.
Whoa.
Also, I see...
Oh, it's you.
You're doing the electricity.
I'm tempted to just go to the portal.
Oh, it's gone now.
Brittle glass.
I see.
Dude, this wand is fun.
I like this more than my brrrr wand actually.
Although imagine if this wand became a brrrr.
That would make this completely insanity.
I mean, it's already insane.
Oh!
Yeah, I'm not getting in there.
Yeah, that's scary.
Way too scary for me, bruh.
Whoa!
The knock back there, I'm almost dead.
Yeah, it's time to leave.
We're getting out of here.
I'm looking for the portal.
Yes, here we go.
Here we go.
Fuck yeah.
Go!
Holy shit.
That was close.
Okay, Stuart.
Come in, Stuart.
Stuart, come here.
Whoa!
It's a mega Stuart.
Oh shit.
Oh no, they're very angry.
Oh, it's ogre.
It's ogre.
Get me!
It's over, it's done.
It's all over.
He can't die.
Ah, fuck.
Omega Stuart.
The hell is that?
Oh man.
Just when I thought I was okay.
Just when I fucking managed to become strong enough to beat Stuart, the game is like, nope.
You gotta go back to fearing the gods.
That's painful.
But you know what?
Let's be honest.
That was a shit run anyway.
I'm better off dead anyway.
Didn't find any proper digging wands or nothing.
It was bullshit.
I have, I have bigger ambitions here.
Don't you sour all this fucking ground with the green shit.
Look at this.
A chest and a wand.
Right when I spawn.
What the fuck?
I am super lucky.
But it's just a rain cloud, so I'm actually not very lucky.
Go this way instead.
Up here.
I can dig though, I have three bombs.
But there's gotta be a way in there that's easier to get to.
When you have three bombs, you gotta be conservative.
What's up here?
I am tempted to make a bomb here.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is it.
Perfect fucking kick, huh?
Amazing.
Now...
Oh, I can't even get in there still.
Oh my goodness.
I gotta swim.
Huh?
I'm using a bomb.
I've had enough.
Do it!
Don't care.
Give me the money.
Take me...
all the way around.
Yeah, that was a bummer.
Back up.
Okay, so what is my plan now?
Hmm...
I mean, I guess I'll just become powerful.
Like always.
I'm so sad though, because I had that portal on me and I was so curious to try it.
It seemed so rare, you know?
I lost that opportunity now.
I couldn't figure it out, dammit.
You're not Barney.
Water?
Also, I just assumed I had water before, by the way.
That could have been the worst kind of thing in that bottle and...
I wouldn't have known.
I was lucky there.
Wow.
Cool.
That was a heart in the middle of that.
Yo, that's sick!
That's a great start.
Compared to last time?
Although it is a little slow.
No, it's good.
This is great.
It's more than enough.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Oh, the freedom!
The freedom!
In the hemisphere!
I'll take this egg.
Thank you.
Also, I don't care.
I can just go through here now.
A chest!
The gods have blessed me!
Dude, I need to find peace with the gods.
Ah!
That was risky.
Glad I made it out alive.
That could have been bad.
That's not bad either.
In fact...
No, actually, come on.
No, it is kind of bad.
It's kind of bad.
Yeah, it's not that good.
It's not that good.
Bap!
Move on.
Did you hear his death rattle?
Never heard that one before.
It went...
Okay, don't collapse the water.
Don't do it.
Oh man.
This rock takes a while to get through.
Why does it not make a sound?
I feel like there's a bug with this spell sometimes.
Like, you need the exact amount of castile or whatever on it and it will make a sound, otherwise it won't.
Even when it goes omega fast, there's still a sound.
Any hearts for me?
Going up here.
Dude, we can get into the dark cave now.
Oh, don't make that mistake again.
Money!
Yes!
Whoa!
Okay, I'm losing too much HP.
Calm the F down now.
Are they both dead?
They look like they're alive.
Look, they're just standing.
Weird.
Fucking Omega Stewart.
Ah, this game keeps throwing nasty shit in my face.
And I slurp it up with a grin.
Most of the time.
Is this guy gonna...
I really need to grab a...
tablet here.
This is... Nope, you know what?
Actually.
Oh yeah, you like that?
Oh shit.
Run!
Whoo!
Oh no, it hit me again.
This is bad.
How are you not dead yet?
There we go.
Thanks.
B.C.
is for grilling.
Wait, don't get watered now.
Water, water, water.
Oh yeah, kill each other.
No, this is bad.
This is bad.
Back, back, back.
Okay, nice.
I feel like it's time to go back, maybe.
I have very low HP here.
But I am able to dig.
Smooth operator.
Oh, he almost sliced me in half.
That was scary.
I think it's time to leave.
We got a 700 gold.
That's not bad.
Let's just get the fuck out of here and move on.
That must be an easier way.
Yeah, I'm going around.
And then hopefully I can use this digging bolt to make something a little faster now.
What do we got?
Nice, nice.
Boo, the beginning was nice.
The rest not so much.
Want experimenter.
That is what I'm taking.
It's either that or vampirism.
That is like the catalyst for a good run.
In my mind.
We got a shuffle one.
Let's see here.
This is very low Castellae.
I need something for the...
Actually, this one is not too bad.
It's a little faster.
Let me see the other ones.
Ah, they all suck.
Actually, that one's good.
That may be the one, but it only has 14 mana charge speed.
Why?
Although this one does cost zero mana.
So, hey!
Hey!
It doesn't matter!
That's amazing.
Lovely.
Okay.
What else?
Let's make...
Let's take this one.
And take that one.
Put these up here.
Let's see here.
3.5 seconds recharge?
Wow.
Yeah, how about no on that one?
What's the best sort of straight up nice wand we have?
It may be this one.
Actually, that one's not bad.
No, it only has three slots.
This one is better.
No, I don't have enough money.
I need three more gold!
That's a disaster!
Ah, that sucks.
That's really bad.
Three more gold.
Guess I'll use this one.
Let's see how it goes.
What if I do something simple like that?
Ah...
It may be okay.
Let's say I'm out here fighting, you know.
Meow, meow, meow.
And I shoot and I walk.
No, that's gonna piss me off in the end.
That's definitely gonna piss me off later.
I know it.
I just know it.
So instead of that, let's try something else.
This one does have...
No, this one...
Seems better.
It's not very exciting.
Better than nothing.
Definitely better than nothing.
Three damage, three damage.
That's probably better than...
Now, any spells I could probably take here, that would be good.
Not even that.
This is a very barebones shop.
Although...
No.
This is actually...
This would be really nice.
That's bad.
That's good!
Maybe it's good enough for the digging, for now.
We don't need to be like... immediately.
This does do eight damage.
Right?
Oh, it didn't even do anything.
Oh, it did, okay.
Like, that's a decent amount of damage right there.
It's not gonna show here.
Because it's bugged.
Yeah, I don't know.
Although, it is nice to just go around and dig shit up.
And this is not bad.
I'm gonna keep it like this.
Put this up here.
Good.
Let's go.
Yeah.
I am not gonna try and anger Stuart.
In fact, I don't even have a means to do it, so...
But look at this, now I can do stuff like that.
This is why it's so good.
I can just grab all the money in the world.
And I guess I can just go back.
Oh, I can't go back now.
I mean, I can.
I can grab the wand still.
You know what?
I'm gonna do that.
Ah, shit.
It's not enough.
How do I get up there?
There we go.
Nice.
Now I'm gonna replace...
by this one.
Replace it with...
There we go.
That's a decent wand.
Will you...
Oh my God!
I do no damage!
He just took me for like so much HP.
This little bastard.
Wow, what a fail.
That was bad.
That was really bad.
Wow, I would have expected that to dig a little faster.
But okay.
Oh no, we've got a...
Oh no!
Where is it?
I gotta kill it immediately.
West, we gotta...
We're gonna have issues later.
What?
Oh, it's Berserkium.
Jesus!
Oh my God!
It's a disaster.
There you are, there you are.
There we go.
Causing trouble here.
That could have gone real bad.
Wait, there's another worm.
There's gotta be...
Look at the width of this tunnel.
There's no way that little worm did that.
I refuse to believe...
Oh, this is scary.
I'm gonna kill him with this.
Heh heh heh heh.
The DPS is good.
My goodness, I keep getting hits.
Toxic sludge, huh?
Fuck me.
I'm not gonna...
Nope.
Hup!
Get it!
Just get in.
It's a disaster anyway.
Let's see what we got.
Teleport, that's nice.
And that's also just a normal teleport, yeah.
Oh well.
Projectile duplication.
No.
Revenge expl...
I hate all of these.
That one is insanity.
Although, I guess, whatever blood money is, it must be amazing.
This is...
Okay, you know what?
This run is kind of a joke anyway.
We're gonna test this.
I need to see what the fuck this blood money is.
I gotta find out.
I... I...
My imagination runs wild.
I'm just gonna fix my shit up first.
Get rid of that.
If we do that, then we do this.
And then we do that.
One, two.
That's, uh...
And that's tup... tup.
That's...
That's decent.
What?
What just happened?
Okay, these are my final wants, I guess.
I can't take it with my wants.
Let's see what this fucking blood money is.
This better be the most amazing shit I have ever seen in my life.
My dude.
Sparkbolt versus sparkbolt, huh?
Like, I can never change my wants?
Did you drop blood money for me?
Uh...
Sure, take it.
Why not?
Oh!
I have this.
I forgot about that.
Oh, my.
Oh!
Bloody gold nugget!
I see.
Every gold heals?
I get it, then.
That's actually kind of wild.
Like, wow.
That is next level wild.
Oh, it's not all the gold.
Oh, I guess I did say may drop.
Oh, then it's not even that good.
Even if all the gold was healing, I'm not sure it was still worth it.
Like, that's how bad it is not being able to edit your wants.
I mean...
Fuck it.
Let's just... this run is a joke now, anyway.
Let's just keep going.
Let's see what's in here.
Okay.
What happens if I pick up Tinko with the ones everywhere now?
You know what?
I'm taking that.
Oh, I need to pick it up.
I'm taking that with me.
We're missioning all the way to the bottom now, and then we're using that.
Uh-oh.
This is a bit scary.
Oh, yeah, this is bad.
This is real bad.
Go!
Damn.
This is wild.
What's that?
Oh, Circle of Unstable Metamorphosis.
Projectile Transportation Field?
What?
Oh, does...
Why would I buy any of these ever?
I can't use them.
Like, it's...
It's a joke.
You know, is this worth joking anyway?
Let's just pick up something else to try.
You teleport away every time you're hurt.
Sure.
Let's try it, man.
Let's see if it's any good.
Oh, why am I...
Yeah, okay, that's what I expected, I guess.
Run!
This is the worst perk in the history of perks.
Why would you take this?
Why?
Yeah, I can't...
Why am I looking at it?
I can't buy it anyway.
Oh, hey!
Passive Fist Reward.
Give me the money I can't use.
What's that, like 50 gold?
That seems super useful, thanks.
Glass Cannon.
You know what?
Sure.
How much damage do I do now?
It's actually a decent amount.
Sure.
I'm definitely dying here, though.
Wait, even my digging is wild?
Water!
I have no more water.
What the...
That's the worst perk ever.
Who would ever pick that up?
It's not a perk, it's a curse.
Wow.
That was funny, though.
That was actually really fun.
Hold on, I gotta turn on some lights.
I'll be right back.
Also, I'm gonna take a piss.
We're back.
And I'm back.
Okay.
I actually wonder now.
I need to check something real quick.
The perk that I just picked up...
Glass Cannon.
Your spells are five times as powerful, but your maximum health becomes 50 and cannot be increased by normal hearts.
What do you mean, normal?
Oh, maybe it's simply the hearts you find versus the...
The hearts you pick up where the sound comes in the back with everyone going...
You know?
Wait.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, I was...
I thought my spells were cut short, but I was hitting a little pixel.
Look at that!
You cannot see that pixel.
That pixel is invisible.
No, you can see it.
It's very small and tiny.
That was weird.
I'm sure this run will be better.
In fact, I feel it.
Ooh!
Berserkium!
Yo!
That's not a bad start.
I would say I may even like it more than water.
Yo, we're back!
We dig again, boys!
We get a second chance.
That's awesome.
And a torch!
Hell yeah!
This is actually a great start.
I'm really feeling this.
Ooh, the...
Dude, the digging with Berserkium is insane in the beginning.
Oh wait, I just need to...
I need to find water.
I need to find another flask and put water in it.
That's really what I need to do right now.
Stay safe.
Let's put this here so we don't confuse it with water.
There's water.
But I want another flask first.
I'm that greedy, okay?
I can allow myself to be a little greedy in the beginning, I think.
It does make stuff like this harder to traverse.
I remember in the beginning of the game, these explosions here looked insane to me.
I mean, they still are nice, but I was just so impressed with the animation of it.
Not everything!
But now, just like there's so many explosions everywhere, I've become accustomed.
Gotcha.
Alright, I can dig.
Let's just dig through shit.
Don't need to walk around.
Like a pleb!
This makes a very worrying sound.
Come on, Matt.
Show me some...
There we go, a flask.
No, it's an egg!
I'll take it, though.
What?!
Someone threw an axe in his face!
What just happened there?
Oi!
Not bad.
Yes!
There we go.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Oh, right.
Drink some of this.
Release the egg!
Kill him!
That was the worst performance I've ever seen.
He died.
Show me those hearts.
There we go.
Aha!
Ooh, nice!
Yeah.
I don't need the bomb anymore.
Now that I can dig...
No, no, no!
Actually, that's fine.
Yeah, that's fine.
We just gotta find some water now.
We gotta empty this potion somewhere.
Let's just empty this.
Where should we empty this?
Probably down here.
Oh, that's a great spot.
Hey, sir!
That's for you.
He didn't care at all!
Hold on.
Look at the digging capabilities now.
Water, water.
Here we go.
Nice!
We have done it!
And we have a torch as well!
That means great things.
Any secrets hiding in here?
I really should go and grab the...
Uh, whatchamacallit?
A tablet.
That's the chest!
Huh.
I...
No.
Nope.
I don't want to take that yet.
Wouldn't make any sense.
I'll take that.
Oh, I thought that was a dynamite!
Alright.
Not bad.
125.
Maybe with the digging capabilities here, I can't go to the top of the mountain.
Nah, but I will still need to destroy the top part.
I don't have enough.
But...
No, I don't have a levitation.
Shit.
I don't have an acceleration, though.
Does that help in water?
I can't tell.
Oh, yeah, it does!
Yo!
That's big.
That's huge.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're not doing that.
Back down, back down, back down.
There we go.
Yes!
And...
Then we get back out.
Easy peasy.
Close one.
Acceleration, man, is the...
best drink ever for that.
In fact, I just love having it on me.
Just drink more of it.
I love the speed.
Boink.
I think it's time to not leave yet.
Hold on.
I'm grabbing the tablet.
Oh, hold on.
I can...
Maybe there's a heart down there.
Go fast.
What's that?
Coal pouch.
I will take it.
Because I want to experiment more with the pouches.
What?
That's not water.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Okay, that wasn't too great.
I'm grabbing the tablet and I'm leaving.
Throwing away the blood.
Thank you.
That's a ramsey, I would say.
In.
Interesting.
Nope.
Nothing exciting.
Oil blood.
Yes.
I shall take it.
That's a good one.
I don't really like most of what I'm seeing here.
Could be okay.
Hold up.
I need something a little faster.
Although...
Yeah.
Shit.
I can't make a good digging wand.
That is Energy Sphere, right?
Return.
I hate all of this.
I'll buy this one, though.
Just because it has a bunch of stuff in it.
I will...
Use these, I think.
I think the best damage here.
That's also not bad.
But I like this more.
Circle of Stillness.
Let's put that...
Let's keep it for now.
That one we can put up here for now.
Yeah.
0.1, 0.8, this is probably better here.
I'm going straight into Fungal Caverns now.
Almost straight.
Whoops!
Ah, fuck.
Wrong order here.
Oh, that's painful.
That's way slower than before.
But...
It works!
This better be good.
Actually not bad.
Oh, but they're the expensive kind.
So kind of bad.
That was actually okay.
Ooh, nice!
The dig is real again.
That's a better digging one right now.
Straight to Fungal Caverns.
Energy Orb.
It's quite something, isn't it?
The great thing about Energy Orb is that it always digs a certain radius.
It doesn't matter how fast you do it.
It digs nicely.
Got it!
Somehow I'm doing really well, which is weird.
I'm not used to doing well.
Is someone behind me?
Look at this!
There's nowhere I can't get through.
Wait, what?
Did someone just get polymorphed?
Okay, that was scary.
We go straight in now.
No fear.
No fear!
Okay, just a bit of fear.
Tiny amount of fear.
Blow it up.
And somehow that fucking toad still lives.
It's unreal.
It's my blood boil.
Oh yeah, I'm Firey Moon!
Forgot about that.
All these runs blend together in my mind.
Sir, do you need help up there?
Maybe I shouldn't have helped you.
I regret.
Come on, show me the good ones in here.
Come on.
This is actually the best one I have right now, just for damage as well.
Oh my god, there's a whole congregation of hammers.
Hamigation.
Dude, I can just wait for this.
This is a money printer.
Look at that.
Make some more.
And then I'm gonna...
Wait, they don't...
Oh, they don't drop money.
Oh, I see.
What a scam.
I thought I just figured out something genius.
The game was ahead of me.
I'm actually liking the energy orb with another energy orb with another energy orb on it.
It's quite nice.
Boink!
Ah, I'm gonna die here.
There's too many of these fuckers.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
I can't see where they are.
Fuck.
He's still alive.
Worst enemies ever.
Show me something good in that one now.
Come on, come on.
Come on, something amazing, please.
That's somewhat amazing.
Let's see it.
Oh, but it's really slow in here because of the air.
Gold pouch!
Well, I'll replace my coal pouch with a gold pouch.
Thank you very much.
This is the most pathetic looking...
...flowing lands ever.
I think the energy orb is also completely...
What do you call it?
Oh, hold on.
Drink this, get rid of it.
Grab that.
I think the energy orb is completely invariant to the gravity situation.
Boink!
Down.
Dude, I'm gonna get high.
Seems like a good use of my time now.
Got him.
Is this shooting one and then three?
Oh yeah, it is.
That makes sense.
Uh oh, uh oh.
It's a little dangerous what I'm doing here.
Shit.
I may die.
Oh!
I'm drinking.
Eat it!
No!
No, no, please no.
13 HP, don't kill me.
I need to get high, please.
Actually, I'm leaving, I'm leaving, I just need to get high.
I'm leaving.
Come on.
No!
Got him.
Okay, quickly eat the mushrooms and get the fuck out.
Get high on the supply.
Hooray!
Eat it all.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Mmm, mmm.
Eat this.
Oh yeah.
Put it in your mouth.
Oh, I'm high as fuck, boy.
Oh shit, I'm tripping.
250?
Okay, that's it.
P-soup.
Has changed into something.
Well, I never see P-soup anyway.
So I don't care.
Whatever.
Oh yeah, we high.
I'm actually feeling dizzy just looking at this.
Whoa.
Oh yeah, we're leaving.
That was scary.
Hey!
Always speed up.
That's dope.
Is that...
Oh, I thought it was Tinker with Wands everywhere.
Um...
Hmm.
I mean...
That's not bad.
But this is also kind of dope, since I'm immune to fire anyway.
Yeah, why not?
Just take it.
I kind of want this...
Oh, hold on, actually.
So this is Shuffle.
I just want one of these, really.
That's not bad.
That's worse.
I do like the idea of these three.
So if I buy this...
with speed up on it...
That's actually kind of dope.
Watch this.
Hey, huh?
These amount of damage there.
Not bad at all.
We could put a fireball orbit on it.
I mean, I am immune to fire.
But am I immune to fireball orbit?
I'm not sure.
I'm going to test...
I'm immune to fire.
What about the explosive effect of it?
I think...
I think I'm immune.
Fireballs, right?
No, fire bolts.
Or these...
This is Fireball.
I think I'm immune.
Everything shall be set on fire now.
I have decreed it so.
Or maybe we put that on something else.
Return.
Um...
This would be a nice...
No, hold on.
Nope.
This is nice.
I like this.
This is a good one for now.
Now for the digging.
That's too slow.
That's better.
Worse.
That's what I like.
I think I like the stillness.
But I'm okay with replacing it if I find something else.
That's better.
Basically, that's where I'm at.
I like that a lot.
Okay.
I don't know if I should put this on.
It is a lot of...
mana spent.
You know, it's...
Yeah, let's just go with it.
It could be fun.
We have a double there.
So we have one with an accelerating shot on it.
Can we use that for something?
Maybe I get rid of this and do that instead.
The ultimate one hit wonder.
Sliced in half.
Mmm, nice.
A little better.
That's way too bad.
That's better, I think.
No, it's not.
Okay, never mind.
I mean, this is nice, but it runs out of mana too quick.
This is okay.
The light goes up here.
And that's it, I think.
That's my setup.
I did grab everything I wanted to, I think.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Move out!
Autobots!
Get sniped.
Oh, oh, dude!
Oh, that's so useful against the frost!
I have a new respect for this perk.
Oh, that's wonderful.
That's incredible.
Asshole.
Lightning bounds with mists.
I doubt mist bounces.
But let me try.
Oh, wait, I automatically ignite it!
Dude.
We could make something here.
Imagine putting a homing on that.
Whoa!
Exquisite me!
Oh, look at all the wands.
Hup!
Yeah, I have a long reload on this, so if I miss...
I'm open to getting shit on here.
I thought that was a worm that fell down at first.
Holy digging!
All of these four dig!
Isn't that funny?
The hell?
Oh, right.
Right.
Yeah.
I should have expected that.
Yep, that makes sense.
That was dumb.
Yeah.
Also, what's happening here?
Oh, I'm slimy.
Get rid of it.
Wash these clothes.
Speak enough.
Is it raining outside?
Hold up, I gotta check.
Fuck, I forgot to pass!
No!
Shit, that was stupid.
I thought I clicked the button when I got up.
Fucking hell, man.
Rookie mistake right there.
Good news is it's not raining.
Whoops.
Look at this.
I don't care about...
Oh man, this perk is actually wild.
I have a completely newfound respect for that with the freezing vapor.
Oh man, that's lovely.
I want to blow that up.
Oh wait, I'm immune to fire.
I don't care.
Everything gets ignited immediately.
Oh, damn.
Yeah.
Yoink.
There goes my life.
Wow, that was also unlucky, man.
I thought I paused the game before.
That was just so unlucky.
Like, I got up from the computer and had the muscle memory of hitting escape.
And I must have taken off my headset at the same time so I didn't hear that it actually did pause.
Rookie mistake right there.
There's not much to say.
I done goofed for sure.
Now we can grab this heart up here.
It's been a while since we've been able to do that.
And this fills me with determination.
I'm not going to lie.
There's a bit of that in there.
Sometimes these balls just don't do what you want them to.
The balls are not cooperating.
Boink.
Oh, that's not enough.
Can we have the tablet, too?
Aww.
It's way too much embedded in there.
I'm not getting that.
I could, probably, with 12 balls, but...
That's okay.
We're going to grab the next one.
Okay, so...
You know what?
Remember in the fungal caverns?
When we brought...
Oh, what was it?
Passilma.
We actually saw this, right?
And, you know, when you get high and you get this message that something has changed...
You actually get this eye symbol, too.
And because it's in the fungal caverns, what if it meant you got to get high three times?
You know?
Do something three times.
And maybe something will open up or whatever.
Wait, what did it say?
Ah, wait.
Speaking of fungal...
Looks like we're already in some kind of fungal situation right now.
That's kind of a coincidence.
It's a wand.
I predict...
There's a black hole in that.
It's a bold prediction.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
How do I get in there?
Probably from upstairs.
Oh, yeah.
Boink!
Burn it.
Oh, this thing's gonna explode.
Oof!
Man, oh, man.
What a mess.
Imagine the smell right here.
It's not even that great.
Oh, well.
Actually, it may be better than what I have right now.
In close quarters, at least.
They do five damage per, so...
kind of a lot.
And they do also explode.
You can dig with this if you're shrewd enough.
But let's not.
Set it on fire.
Water myself.
Go.
Where are you hiding?
There you are.
I like the color change...
in the hemisphere here.
With the fungal stuff.
Makes it feel very muted.
Oh, that doesn't even...
That works.
I need a tablet.
So I can earn some bucks.
Oh, he has a wand, sir.
What are you doing with that?
Let's see what's on it.
It's a bit risky.
Oh, all seeing eye.
All right.
Oh, my goodness.
Okay, that's bad.
Oh, fuck, this is bad.
I'm not ready for you guys here.
This is the worst.
I can't kill them.
Why do they have so much HP?
These little fuckers.
With a bajillion HP.
I'm getting owned here.
What the fuck?
Sure.
It's like General Grievous.
Collecting lightsabers.
Oh, I want to get high right now.
Eat them, eat them, eat them, eat them.
I think I need about...
between 200 and 250.
And then it happens.
So I'm actually going to prepare for that.
And then I will try to find Pasilma.
And go back to Fungal Caverns.
I think that makes a lot of sense.
The more I think about that, the more it makes complete sense.
But I have to do that.
Oh, shit.
20 HP.
Quick.
Oh, wait.
Get high!
Quick.
Eat the mushrooms.
Before the cops come.
146.
I need more.
I need more than that.
Oil potion.
All right.
Levitation?
Thanks.
I like that.
A lot.
That was almost really bad.
Nah, you know what?
We're leaving.
Nope.
Too many explosions and I can't see shit because I'm tripping.
Shit spells on shit once.
I like toxic immunity, actually.
Worm attractor.
Worms find you attractive.
No, I don't want rat friends.
Give me toxic immunity.
Just give it to me.
Is that...
No.
I want energy orb.
Okay.
Well, this I can work with, I think.
I've got two doubles.
And some luminous drills.
How much does that cost?
Ten mana.
Ooh.
That's cool.
I need a faster mana charge, though.
This is way too slow.
Whoops.
Oh, that's not bad.
I mean, for a quick dig.
Maybe this is even better.
No, it's actually worse.
Actually, I'm not sure.
It's about the same.
Let's just do that.
And we have this guy right here to do some vision.
And then we need some damage, which we don't really have.
Eh...
What can we get?
Yeah.
Why not?
Let's go with that.
Shoot two of them at a time.
Decent damage.
And then we can freeze enemies as well if we need to.
I like it.
Oh.
Good start.
That was actually really fun.
Oh, what a shot!
What a shot!
My dude has aim.
Wait, am I destroying it?
Oh, no!
I think I'm destroying it.
Yeah, look.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I can't dig for gold with this.
That is unfortunate.
Oh, much better.
It's great.
Good damage.
Oh, that's oil.
Just swimming in oil.
They're rich.
I think I want to go back to the fungal caverns.
I want to get high.
Ah, no thanks.
That's very inaccurate.
100 crits?
Damn.
The gold itself was blocking the liquid from rolling downhill.
That's kind of funny.
Wait, am I...
What does this guy do?
What did that aura do?
Cool.
Already two HPs found down here.
Much better than my average.
Which is one or zero.
Oh my god, it's raining lava.
If you think about it, the second stage here is actually insanely difficult.
Imagine you just start this game.
This place is nuts.
So many dangers everywhere.
Can enemies bleeding lava and shit?
I can't hit.
Nah,
I hate this digging.
The dick sucks.
I give this dick two out of five.
No, 1.5.
That's the maximum.
Actually, it's worse than that because I can't even go for the gold.
Get rid of that one and then do a...
No, I mean do a...
There we go.
That's more like it.
You want some?
Do you like these sawblades?
Masterful dodging on my part there.
I felt really cool just now.
I got him though.
He was just dancing around those sawblades.
Water.
What is this?
Levitation.
I'll use that a bit.
Ring around the rosy.
Got it.
Wait,
it's not dead yet.
I feel like fungal caverns is getting to be more and more of a pipe dream now.
I have just too little HP.
I'm going to get my shit shoved in.
Hey!
I was part of myself.
I let the spacebar go there so I could drop.
Goes against my natural instinct.
But I did it.
I want to tickle this guy's feet.
He died from it.
The power of the tickle.
Should I just go?
Yeah, let's go.
I'm feeling a goat.
And what do we got?
Giant firebolt.
Dew spread is nice.
What's that?
Gold is forever.
Gold nuggets never disappear.
I mean, I don't really have an issue grabbing them, I guess.
But wait, does that also mean if enemies kill each other off screen?
The gold is just going to be there.
That could maybe not be the worst.
Hold on, let me see if I can make a decent one first things first.
With the money that I have.
I like this.
Yes.
Ooh, what?
Ooh, dude.
Hold on.
We could do something here.
This dig is terrible anyway, we're not going to use it.
Yeah, this is much better.
And then we do a double.
Into saw blades.
I wonder, does it always get absorbed by the enemy I hit?
Wait.
Oh!
Okay, it doesn't.
Unless the statue doesn't count as an enemy?
Fuck.
All right, cool.
That was very exciting.
Although this does cost 20 mana, I could do something like this.
And each of them will...
Okay, maybe that's not good.
It's a bit too fast.
It's way too inaccurate, so you know what we do?
We get this.
Oh, that's much better.
Holy shit.
That's actually pretty dope.
I like it.
And then we have circle of stillness.
How about we do a missile?
Or that?
No, that's only limited.
But so is this, I guess.
I'm going to missile some fools.
Because I'm going to be throwing away these wands anyway, so whatever.
Uh, yeah.
Let's get an extra HP.
Or life.
Let me try this missile.
Boink.
All right, it hits them.
Does it automatically track?
Oh, it does!
Oh, don't stand in the freezing vapor.
Not bad.
I like.
Let's not overdo it.
He's dragging the wrong one.
I got it.
We already lost almost half HP.
It's a disaster.
But only because we had to do a bit of testing in the lab.
It is to be expected.
That doesn't dig at all.
So we have no dig right now.
It's very annoying.
We can't even get in here.
Maybe from below.
Let
me through.
Boy, you are about to shot me in the face.
Dope.
Is that?
No.
I thought it may have been worm blood.
I mean, this wand is kind of nice, but it's not like amazing.
It's just nice.
That's it.
A nuke!
Don't mind if I do.
How about I try it?
Hey, guys!
Holy fuck!
Oh, shit!
Everything's collapsing.
Yo, that was a big-ass explosion.
Holy crap.
Imagine putting that and have it infinite.
Infinite nuke.
You gotta need explosion immunity for that, of course.
You know, I could have died easily there.
If I wasn't shielded by the terrain there, I would have died.
I'm pretty sure.
I got lucky.
I was expecting the range to be similar to the holy hand grenade.
Acid.
Nah.
I skip.
What's that?
It's a gold nugget!
It's like a mini Heezy base here.
Whoo-hoo!
Bastard!
Didn't even see you there.
Where are you coming from?
Huh?
50 HP, I gotta leave.
Oh, we're being sniped now.
Go!
Oh, that was close.
Hey.
Get missled.
Can't even get through the glass.
I mean, ice.
Shuffle is kinda crazy on that.
I think I'm leaving.
It's not going too well here.
I'm definitely a bit shaky.
I can't even purchase anything.
What's that?
Holy shit.
Are those nukes?
A bunch of nukes with fireball orbit on it.
Oh, no!
I need the money.
I need to purchase this wand immediately.
Ooh.
That's a guaranteed long run.
But that one is also amazing.
We gotta go with this.
That's a guaranteed win now.
Easy.
Game has been beat.
That's all you need.
Isn't that sweet?
I don't have money for shit.
I will make a good wand out of this.
And when I say good wand, I just mean a singular...
lightning bolt.
That's all you need, baby.
friendo!
I saw you.
Circle of stillness is...
Nah, that's just...
You know what?
It could come in handy here.
Of all places, this is the spot.
And I don't think I like this very much.
Maybe I changed my mind on that.
This is my primary damage.
I don't care.
I'm going all out on that.
I don't have explosion immunity.
That's the one thing.
So, that's a bit sketchy.
I'm sure I'll survive.
Worst case, I will...
Wait, wait, wait.
I mean, I do have this wand, I guess.
I'll use that as my backup.
I'm going to freeze and then that.
That's the backup situation.
If things go... get a little hairy here.
Alright, let's go.
friendo, you need to survive.
You know what?
Actually, I'm going to switch these two around.
Watch me speedrun this shit right now.
Ultra precision gameplay.
High skill ceiling.
Skill ceiling reached gameplay.
Oh yeah, did you see that?
MLG.
A common maneuver in the circuit.
Let's go the other way.
I can't even dig.
I need to find a digger.
That's actually super important.
friendo, I hope I get to find some pheromones so we can have a bit of fun together.
Okay.
There's way too many of these down here.
That's for you.
No, I'm stuck.
Ooh, that's scary, that's scary, that's scary.
Okay, we lost a lot of HP.
It's okay though.
That was not part of the plan, I gotta admit.
That came a bit out of left field for me.
I can't dig.
We gotta get to the portal.
Yeah, it's not going so well.
Run.
We gotta wait for that to rise and disappear.
The only way.
Okay.
How are you still going?
It's tough when you can't dig, huh?
Like I literally can't go anywhere.
It's just the worst.
Too many explosives.
There's too many explosives.
This has become a survival operation.
We're not here to explore, we're here to survive.
No, no, no, no, we're at 5 HP.
Oh, that's bad, that's really bad.
I think it's over.
There's no way I survive.
I can't dig.
Get rid of that.
We wait.
Oh, I need to... I need pheromone so bad!
Wait, what do I have?
Levitation, oil, water, that's useless!
Let me get rid of that.
Anything want to shoot me?
Plenty of things want to shoot me.
There's a sniper down there.
He's still down there.
I'm gonna...
Hmm, what am I gonna...
Don't mess with me, bruh!
That was sweet.
Cold and calculated.
Precision gaming.
Yep, yep.
I don't like big open spots like this.
Great, that's scary, that's scary.
Yikes.
Dig!
Oh, oh no.
Machine guns are the worst right now.
I'm scared of that electricity.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
You.
Gotcha.
I hear the portal.
We're almost home, boys.
We're almost home.
We gotta play this sweet and slow.
Who else is down there?
That was scary.
Damn.
Okay, very nice.
What's this?
Wanda radar.
That's... I don't want any of this.
I'm gonna re-roll.
Ah, ha!
Hold up.
Let me think.
Oh, I thought it was homing!
Fuck!
I don't have a stone anyway, I guess.
But, you know.
Unlimited spells, huh?
You know what?
I gotta get it.
There's just no other... there's no other... there's... of course.
Of course I gotta get that.
I gotta get that.
Dude.
What if we trigger this?
Huh?
We have infinite.
Everyone gets frozen.
Frozen into...
Oh, acid.
Also, I need that one.
Thanks.
Shit, I don't have money.
Dang it.
I guess I can make missiles.
Yo, infinite missiles?
Infinite missiles!
That can't damage me, right?
I mean, it does say damage explosive.
I think it can.
But it doesn't follow me, right?
It seems to be going down towards an enemy down there.
Yeah.
Let's make it fast.
Make it fast.
I guess it doesn't matter which direction this is being shot.
It's always gonna...
Okay, never mind.
It doesn't matter.
Well, well, well.
Make it faster?
Wait, why does it take so long?
Oh!
It adds half a second of recharge.
That explains it.
I was wondering.
All right.
Well...
I think I still want a lightning bolt.
Just because it's so good.
And then maybe...
You know what?
Maybe we put a nuke?
No, a summon missile.
At the end of a trigger.
How about that?
I think that sounds pretty dope.
Let's see.
We gotta put it on a non-shuffle.
Huh?
That's pretty cool.
I like it.
And maybe we add some...
something something to this.
What if we do a double...
triple?
One, two...
Oh, wait.
One, two, one...
Oh, do we even have money for this?
I mean, mana.
Nah, this is bad.
I mean, that's one hell of a bang, but...
Maybe that's too much.
This seems okay.
It's like a slap in the face when things need to get serious.
I like that.
And then we have this guy teleporting around.
Very cool.
Bubble spark.
And that's our...
This is gonna be our main.
It sounds insane, but...
Hear me out.
It's gonna work.
And we have teleport.
And that one.
Okay.
That's it.
Let's get a move on.
Oh, that's actually kind of annoying.
Shit.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Okay, okay.
I don't like this wand.
I hate it.
We're going back to that one.
Wait, what?
Oh, he's summoning them!
I get it, I get it.
I thought he was emitting healing for some reason.
I get it now.
Okay, that was a bit of a chaotic start there.
I'm definitely gonna kill myself with this weapon, but...
It is what it is.
You can't be afraid of the weapon.
Otherwise, the weapon will own you.
You know?
Gotta show that weapon who's boss.
And then you can tame it.
I'm already making my way towards the portal, as you can tell.
Maybe I'll collect a bit of money first.
Just so I can purchase something in there.
Like, this lightning bolt is doing pretty good.
Against these spiders.
Wait, I'm not immune to fire.
Stop burning.
Oh, what's that?
It's a blue...
Oh, teleport man.
Shit!
I'm going!
I need a black hole so I can get back up.
I can't purchase anything.
What is this?
Always casts random ass something?
I just want the perks here.
Ooh!
We're gonna gamble.
Angry ghost.
An extra item in Holy Mountain.
I guess in the next Holy Mountain.
Copying nearby spells and projectiles.
Hmm.
We have made it.
To the vaults.
What have we really, though?
God damn it!
Don't fall, Glenn.
My priorities have changed.
I'm going for a win.
There's no way I can make my way back up unless I find a black hole or something.
Something like that.
Which I doubt.
Huh.
That makes it a bit scary, though.
I will take it.
Let's see how bad it is.
What?
The fuck just happened?
I must have hit some kind of mage?
It's my thinking.
You.
Come up here.
What?
Oh, he's spawning those guys.
Oh, that's annoying.
No, it's over.
It's over.
There's no way I survived.
What?
I'm stuck.
Oh, fuck.
The bomb.
Wait, what?
I'm a 74 HP now.
I thought I was at much less.
That was scary AF.
Water myself.
We're taking the portal.
First sign of portal we go.
Shit.
The spells.
I don't have money for it anyway.
Go!
Hahaha.
Ooh.
That's scary as fuck.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, I don't have money for any of this anyway.
I saw the damage increase there.
What do we got, man?
Tell me we got something good.
Uh, bombs materialized.
I don't know about that.
I'm gonna reroll.
I don't even know what I'm hoping for.
Strong levitation.
You can fly 100% long?
That doesn't sound too bad, actually.
Kills to mana.
You know what?
I think I like that.
Being able to levitate for longer is...
seems like a good survival skill right now.
Yeah.
I'm poor as fuck.
Oh, man.
Come here.
What?
Oh, come on.
That's bullshit.
What just happened there?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, there's no way.
I'm stuck.
Hahaha.
I got ganged.
I got ganged up on.
Frozen and ganged up on, man.
I mean, I had no ambition of actually making it through this place.
However, if I made it to the very end, maybe there was a chance that I could have killed the end boss.
But having to go through this place?
Yeah, I doubt it, man.
That's a bit...
That's a bit of a tall order.
There's no way I would have made it through there.
Yeah.
Okay, that was fun, though.
I experimented with some new perks and all that last time as well.
The perk, the run before that.
But I'm going to stop now because I got to go in just a second here.
This was kind of a...
This was actually a decent run we had today.
Tried some new perks.
Bit of chaos.
That was fun, though.
How's everybody doing?
I want to tell them.
Should we tell them?
Don't tell me anything.
Unless there's something bugged in the game.
Oh.
Wait.
Fuck.
I had vampirate...
This run or the run before?
Was it this run or...?
Oh, no, I forgot.
Guys, this is my biggest blunder ever.
I told you my brain didn't work today, man.
Ah, shit.
Fuck.
Oh, that's bad.
That's a new level of bad.
Fuck.
How did I forget that?
That's horrible.
Oh, okay.
Next time for the next stream.
Someone said...
What did you say?
Hold on.
I missed it.
You need the alcohol.
Exactly.
Next time I play this game...
I'm gonna actually get beers.
Because it is what's...
It does help me.
I'm getting the alcohol next time.
We're getting the IPAs out.
It's gonna be a half drunk stream for sure.
Because that is the only way I get through this.
Definitely.
I can't believe it.
I'm so sorry.
You guys must have been suffering.
So bad.
Oh, I feel terrible.
And the worst part is...
Vampirism.
I even said it.
That's it.
That's the run.
Now I can't lose.
I said that.
And I completely forgot I had it.
Ah, that's terrible, man.
That's so sad.
At least you saw Scott today.
We were waiting for...
Oh, is that the name for the other God?
Steven Scott?
Oh, man.
Did I like Omega Stewart?
I actually...
I thought he was pretty cool.
He was a lot bigger too.
The name is Scout.
Ah, what does that mean in Finnish?
Let's find out.
Finnish to English.
Scave.
Hold on, what is a scave?
I don't even know that...
English to Danish.
Scave.
Oh.
Like peeling or pushing.
I see.
We're calling Scott Big Steve.
I like that.
Scotty.
Scoot.
Oh.
What does that mean?
Oh, it doesn't mean anything.
Oh, with a K.
I'm dumb.
Hold on.
It means look.
Okay.
Anyway, that guy was a surprise for sure.
I was not expecting him to show up.
I was expecting his little brother to show up.
The one I had no trouble with.
Basically a cop.
It's like, Halt!
You're under arrest.
For breaching the holy mountain numerous times.
How dare you.
Mortal!
I have seen you breaching the grounds for the last time.
I, Scotty, shall show you pain.
Criminal skull.
I love that phrase.
It was nice you tried a different build in your first run.
I mean, at first I really tried to make the build I usually make.
Okay, it's like I was forced into another build, which I'm happy about.
In hindsight now.
But I couldn't make the build that I wanted to make work.
So I got forced into thinking along a different way.
And it worked out.
Now I have another plan for spells in the future.
You know?
Making wands hit hard, but slow.
Basically have a trigger with a million pieces of crap inside of it.
It's actually amazing.
I can't wait to try more of that combination.
I think it was more fun than the...
you know?
The machine gun was awesome in the beginning, but it gets a little old fast.
So I was looking to try new things as well.
I think that's why I enjoy the lightning bolt so much.
Because it's such a...
smack when you use it, you know?
Just feel the impact.
You feel the damage you do.
I love that.
Oh, by the way, guys.
On Thursday, we're going to be starting...
Slay the Spire.
That's the game that won the poll.
And I will still be streaming Noita.
Just sort of alternately.
Not like one-to-one, like switch it up all the time.
But like maybe some days, two times Slay the Spire.
And then other days, I'll do more Noita and sometimes more Slay the Spire.
It'll be a little mixed up, I guess, depending on how I feel.
And how things go.
Who knows?
Maybe I won't even like the game.
We'll have to see.
But I'm excited nonetheless.
I voted for Slay the Spire but didn't think it would win.
My money was on Skyrim.
People are saying Skyrim is a little dated by now.
But, you know, I'm still willing to give it a try.
Drunken Slay the Spire stream.
Slay the Spire is a card game, right?
I mean, that's what I think at least.
I saw the screenshots and there were cards.
So I'm gonna have trouble with it, basically.
Because it's my second card game ever.
Next to inscription.
Try Oblivion.
So that's also the Elder Scrolls.
But it's a little older, right?
I asked on the Discord whether or not I needed to play them in order to understand them and people said no.
So I think I wanna try Skyrim first just to get into the universe.
Because it's also a very beloved...
Like, a very beloved entry.
I basically know all the memes about it, you know?
Like, the waking up in the beginning meme.
On the card or whatever.
I've seen that a million times on the internet.
And also, you know, the arrow in the knee and all that.
I know about that stuff, but that's pretty much most of it.
Oblivion is Elder Scrolls IV, Skyrim is V.
Yeah, okay.
You would recommend Oblivion before Skyrim?
Is it not a bit too dated, you think?
People are saying Skyrim is already a little too dated.
But I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
We'll have to see.
They all have a timeline in the lore, but the gameplay are not connected.
Okay.
That's cool.
I remember reading about Oblivion in a German gaming magazine back in the...
Well, what is it even now?
Two thousand... Between 2000 and 2010.
I don't remember exactly when.
But I remember looking at the gaming magazine and seeing the graphics and was blown away by it.
Holy shit, that looked insane.
Back then.
The best thing in Elder Scrolls is quests and story, not the visuals.
Yeah, I would assume so.
It's an RPG, right?
Does that make sense?
I mean, it's not that I can't play games that are not pretty or anything.
I play plenty of old games.
So that's not gonna be an issue for me, I don't think.
Okay, guys, I'm gonna grab some grub.
And then I'm gonna head on to bed soon.
So thanks for watching.
Let's raid someone.
I forgot to do that last time, by the way.
Let's see, who's streaming Noiter right now?
Someone is streaming who says, ah, so Noiter means wizard.
Let's raid him.
Guys, thanks for watching and hanging out.
It's always a pleasure.
Enjoy, pray.